Fracturing it's
That's
This song is practically what it's all about
Oh
Breakdown let's break down that song
That was the best part Z you talked over it, man. That was the best part
No, you're disabled thing you would take a look go to let me turn my camera on I do is we don't
Go you sweetheart
Okay, I like that. I like that. It's okay. Hey some things some things are sad some things are sad
Joe say hi to say hi to say hi to Katie Joe
Well, let me look at the chat. Let me see who's in there
What up, Katie, Jamie's Cowboys, come on, sweetheart.
So now, say hi to everybody.
What are you doing?
How are you?
Are you really crying?
I'm not crying, baby.
I'm so used to joining good times and like I can't see the chat because you don't pay $7. Oh, it's actually going to jail tomorrow
So
Well, that's all say a perp or good times because tomorrow is a score day. He's going to jail. Are you serious?
Yes. Yes, but this is by the time I go to sleep tomorrow. My best friend good times is going to be in jail
What if and he is my best friend?
Is it the DUI to get caught?
Yeah, go ahead.
You got to pay.
Yeah, if you want to drink and drive, you got to pay the prices.
You got to pay the piper.
You got to pay the piper, Niki.
Well, you know, you know, how long is he going to be in there?
Do you know?
You know what?
I'll be sitting there for a long, long time.
I'll be sitting there for a long time.
Like, oh, good times.
You need some coffee.
You need some.
You need some commissary, old dog.
Look oh, somebody sent me money like Nick. I got other things to do my money. I gotta pay my electric bill
I don't got time to send you money for a couple soup. Okay. Well, how long is it?
I hope he's in there for a little bit. I listen I hope he's in there for at least a year. I hope
Could you imagine what good times would do tomorrow they're like, sir
You're a good guy, but we got a sent you to one year in jail
He'd be like, oh my god, what are we gonna do?
Oh my god that I you know, it's actually pretty cool that I don't know if you guys know this
But it's a pretty cool thing like beta actually had her birthday. She's actually a half a century
She's over a half a century old like wow beta. You're pretty cool. You're over a half a century old
It's pretty cool. It's all to you yo
fucking time bomb.
You know what? Happy birthday to Bita.
Happy birthday to Bita.
Yeah.
I'm talking to you anymore. I'm banned from my channel.
But like, right?
It's like the old lady's like she's almost like her grandma.
Like Bita don't even know.
Like somebody's like, I don't even know what you're saying.
Yeah, cause you're getting old dumb ass.
Your brain's going away.
You fucking old lady.
Well, I'll beat the, I'll do the best.
Especially in the A.R.
No, you're not the best, Dita.
You're a bitch.
Now, you're not the best.
Well.
That's what the fuck the word is.
Can I say one thing?
Can I say one thing, Suggie?
Can I at least say one thing, please?
Sure.
Go to everyone.
The other day I tried to join beat a stream and she's like Joe, are you gonna interrupt us all the time?
Like you let these fucking retards on your stream and I get I get questioned
But you know why you know what happy birthday you'll bitch
No, I'm never talking to that horrible
the
You know what my birthday is Ashley? I don't ever tell my birthday, but my birthday is coming up and thank you
So it means a lot to you know a cool guy
Let me let me finish sir a cool guy like if a cool guy like psyche has my back
Then I know I must be doing something right
Well, you know I cool guy because you have my back because you know I'm going through controversy right now
And you know RG has formed on me
you know I got all of that fucking missing let me say one thing and I don't I don't really get into drama
But that fucking loser RG is a loser nor Cal. There's another fucking loser for you
These guys are in their fucking 50s and 60s. They're like
Like RG, I think RG's a mod for Bita.
Like make it sweet to scream, you fucking loser.
Right, I mean, the doctor, the doctor really,
the doctor called her like aunt or something,
like, or their family's store.
Oh, no.
Yo, let me tell you what.
I don't want to be rude, psyche,
but have I ever seen RG in real life?
I would knock that, can I say the N-word?
I would say I'd knock that N-word out,
is what I would say.
That's where I, I'm not gonna say it,
but that's where I would say it.
You know, Alexander and I are bringing the word back.
I mean, it's like, you know, I'm like, she,
you know, she's kind of spearheading the campaign, but I support the campaign to like, you know,
same guy got a role of duct tape. I can borrow a second, like a duct tape. RG's hands behind his
back and like kill him. Hello. Okay. Am I a Minecraft video game? Okay. Well, please. Am I immortal
prominent in like in the video game? I'm saying, yeah, I'm gonna kill him and more games is a video
Yeah, so and also cue porn bomb me. Um, they're saying, oh, you're a pdf supporter. You have a pdf
Yo member one time to listen to live in Pittsburgh and he was like yelling the M word like he does all the time
And like some black guy heard him like they live next to him through the walls
Hold on
Hold on don't listen don't listen to me
He was like living in Pittsburgh Q was and like some neighbor heard him say the M word and you're like
Why are you saying the fucking and cue with this and I swear to God
It's like he cues like and like excuse us like
it was for history like i knew the m word i'm just saying it for like history's sake
and that nigga moved yo the nigga had to move to california the nigga had to get the fuck up
out of here like i swear to god psyche i don't mean to be the toughest guy up here but have i
ever seen q 45 in real life i'd slap him and say what the fuck are you going to do about it
Like Q45 is a piece of shit to me on the bottom of my shoe on the bottom of my work boots
Q45 is a piece of shit told it you understand now
Are you taking a piss are you in your bathroom?
Yo the other night I swear to God I like felt like I had to take a shit and I ripped a fart
It was like a 19 second fart. It was 19 seconds long. It's like
Can I, can I describe it to you?
You might want to describe it for me.
I really don't want to hear about it.
All right, I'll buy it.
All right, all right, good.
But it was like...
Oh my God.
Well, that sounds terrible.
Well...
I was like, I was like, wow, nice to meet you, cow.
He's like, it's not a cow.
That was your ass.
He was like, oh.
Okay, wow, wow, you know, um, okay. Wow. Okay. Well, that's one thing I will say at least you're good
At least you're good. Look, it's like you turn your cow. At least you ain't a coward
At least you ain't a little coward that don't turn the camera on that's one thing I will give you credit for man
At least you ain't a coward
Well, if you really saw some of these people that they really looked like you'd be kind of like, you know, shocked
I mean, you're kind of handsome in a way. You're actually kind of gay. Are you gay?
I am gay I'm gay I don't know I don't I think I'm gonna have to sleep
Remember one time there was like a swing and bridge at a state park and Kate walked on it
You're like whoa, whoa, we don't like 300 pound pigs on this bridge
And they're like Kate you gotta know. Excuse me. Can I please finish there was like a nice little swing and bridge at the state park
Where I live, but like I'm like Kate, but like if Kate walked on it, you'd be like listen
We don't let just anybody walk on this bridge.
And if you're over a 300 pounds, you've got to sit back.
They named her Big Ben, but I don't know if he's
going to clock over the...
I'm not going to love about Sandman. He will fuck anything.
and you get a 700 pound woman in front of Sam and he'd be like oh shoo-loo-loo-loo-law
god would have fucked that thing have like Sam and calm down bro but you can't even get
your head into her pussy she's 700 pounds and you're gonna try to lick her ass well you know
there are some black guys that are like on like my 600 pound life there's like you know there's
like these skinny black guys what was that noise what was that noise you got snacks
You guys know I got a I got a new phone today. I got a new
5g phone
The other day or the other week it wasn't the other day
But it's like two weeks ago or five weeks ago
It's like two months ago
But I had to get a new phone because I lost it at the Orville's opening day game
I went to the Orville's game my friend that lost my friends. I was so drunk
But I swear to God, I never thought phones mean a lot to me, like the internet.
But I almost had a panic attack, like, oh my God, I need my phone, damn it.
Can I talk to Scythe here, Samette?
Yeah.
I died, I was inside.
Well, that's terrible, I mean, but my new phone is great, though, and I'll show you guys what it looks like.
I mean, it's like, I mean...
Show it, show it, please.
Shout out, where'd I put it?
Whoa, nice ass.
Nice ass, by the way.
Oh my god, I'm sorry.
Okay, my brother's a little bit messy.
Nice grow up, Chad.
Chad needs a grow up.
Yeah, oh my gosh. I hope you didn't see anything. Okay. Well, let me see and I'm right now we saw where we enjoyed it
We saw that and we enjoyed it. Okay. Well, I am well, so I'm showing
Now you're trying to show it now you're bending over a little I am
I need to call I need someone to call it
It's almost someone call me
One thing I will say your hair grown out you look I like the hair grown out
I will say come on that hair is growing look like I don't have no hair under
I'm not gonna show my head, but it's like if I if I grow I would love that long fur
But then again one thing I always thought I
Never want to grow I can't grow a beard like a big beard
But if I think cut my hair it would be like a wispy beard
But the point is I always like lay my head on the pillow when I go to bed
And I can't like stand when I have like a little bit of hair on my face
And like I can like feel it on the bed like it's winter. It's summer
And it's already hot in here by the way.
I don't need a fucking.
What is it like to have like your pubic hair
the color of Cheetos?
Actually one time I met this girl when I was like,
she wants me to have a beer and I shaved my pubes
included to my face and she kissed me.
And I was like, hey, did you enjoy it?
She's like, it tastes good Joey.
So what are you gonna say about that psyche
along here?
She's like Cheetos cause Cheetos tastes good.
She was like, who's that little gay guy Chino?
I was like, oh, he's like a little Dorito.
Oh, but beat a bone in beer when he was 19
because she's a fucking old freak.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Oh, she did.
Oh, I don't know what I'm saying.
Oh.
Wow, I remember what it was so lonely. Remember what Bita was so lonely
She had to buy an underage guy beer cuz like she need to get fucked so bad
Like she all by Cheeto beer even though he's 19. I'm Bita. I'm so
I didn't mean to say
Thank you so much
That's where my camera off. Okay. So well, I know but I'm in all you know
I'm in all this controversy right now or whatever everyone's like a lot of people are mad and you know
I was getting you know, at least I had to hide like at least a hundred people the other day because
Yeah, bald Garfield with the cheeto. Somebody just called me bald Garfield. This is look like bald Garfield to you you piece of shit
This is a psyche. This is how I wear my hat like I'm like Walker. I like what you say to me boy
I'm sad about shoe blue blue. I'll wear my ass that way biggie. You know
I think I have a picture of Sam
Even those eyes behind you why those eyes crossed you fucking cross-eyed as well
Excuse me. Hold on one second. I have pictures of a side. No, don't excuse you
Are these are these pictures of Sam and I do recognize this person right here here
It's a black screen to me. Oh my god. What the hell is that?
That's what the fuck am I looking right there? You're playing you that's a man bear
Sammy you gained a lot of old big ol seven fat seven got some videos there. Yeah, here is that there he's crying here
Um, that's they know they're just a psyche. Can you do me a favor look up?
You don't got to look it up
But if you if anybody looks up the Baltimore Earl's we have a reliever a bullpen picture named rica Garcia
He looks exactly like Jay dog. There's be there's dead serious. Oh, yeah, J dogs. Yeah, I think J dogs ban
There's beta in the picture. Here's beta
No, that'd be that's a that's a compliment to be the beta does not look that good. Okay
Okay, and then I have Kate the turtle
Okay, are you there?
Happen to show oh here
Uh-oh, why are you so wrong?
That's what they that's what they all said. Why is it so little? Thanks a lot. No, it's like why is it so little go?
That was a comment to be the beat it did not look as good as that lady that you just
Go take a shit you gotta at least take a post
You might want to turn my camera off one time good time said if I turn my camera off, you know what I see
Let me show you one thing right here. Okay. Oh your flesh is one
Let me show you what they need you to look at the forearm look at the arms and look at the fucking definition
I thought you had to take a piss like you all you want to see a show
I got it. Look at the left arm. You were the other side. You got the oh that was all damn
No, be honest. This is a $9,000 watch
I'm just kidding. Okay. Wow, that looks beautiful. I actually found it on the Titanic. It was this is actually on the Titanic
Anniversary the Titanic, isn't it was it yesterday or today was anniversary? They're all in their life boats a thousand years ago
In my dreams I see
I love you you're beautiful
You're cute. I love when Bita puts a T on the end of every word.
You're beautiful. I see you.
I remember when Psyche, if I was, I'm not gay, but if we were on the Titanic,
I would stand on the edge of the shit with you, like on the bow, and be like, we're the king of the world!
You flex for me on the how about if we have oh oh you want some more are you
have you want some more here you go here's a little piece is a little piece
actually you know what let me put a sleeve up let me put a sleeve up if you
ever want to piece now I really want to turn you on big dog take a look at oh
my second look at the four or take a look at the arm in the in the lights
Oh, nigga, I can crush your balls.
Oh, okay.
That's my ball in your top.
I'm just kidding.
Okay.
That's all right.
I got, you know what?
I got to turn it off.
Okay, there we go.
That was a little too far.
That was a little too close.
I'm sorry.
I'm worried about it.
Go take a piss or something.
Did you just say you had to take,
why do you have a saddle?
Oh, that's your legs?
Oh.
Yeah, my legs in the psyche. One thing I always fuck with you about is you never let these losers that come up at you
Oh my god, is that little nor?
Lola Lola black Lola
Lola my god, I'd even see her first
I was looking at your gay legs and then I seen that little cat. Oh my god. Look at that angel
Yeah, that's an angel right there
Yeah, all right. Yeah, look at her little paws. Look at her little paws
Lenore's right here. That's
But then you say yeah, oh my god, what an eye. I'm sorry. Hold on the doors right here. I'll take I'll take out the background
Here
You see my jack-in-the-box and stuff hey Lenore that and Joe
Lenore God bless you Lenora all on seeing up there
Reads around to here. I'm gonna put my back around again
Okay, well, how are we doing tonight?
Yeah, so, I mean, it's nice to have you on the panel
and it's like, and thank you because it's like,
you know, so many people like about a pressure
and are afraid to even talk in the chat.
Well, you know what I love, at least it's Friday.
Hell yeah.
Thank God it's Friday, it's Thursday actually.
It's Thursday actually.
What?
It's Thursday?
Oh my God, I gotta go, I gotta go.
Oh no.
Well, it's almost Friday.
I thought it was Friday.
I thought it was, thank God, it's Friday.
outside right now or he's maybe in the bedroom like where he's around and uh yeah oh baby uh
you know do you remember i love good times and i'm not talking about good times i swear i'm not
talking about good times but remember one time he let his cat out for like 20 hours like good
time just get your ass up and go check on your cat you fucking bum sorry about that well i'll get a
You know, bro psyche sometimes like when I see like fucking beat a guy. I love beta. I don't love beta
I like either but when I see beat a good live and these faggots like Sam and or black RG or kissing her ass
It's like these fucking loot like black RG is one of the biggest losers on that
plane to earth and like I have to sit here and put up with these fucking loot you know that's why I
haven't even joined anymore. I had a form bomb me but I put up the screen. How are you? Cheers Suggie.
Cheers. Cheers. His form bomb made me from backstage. RG's the one of the biggest fucking
nigga make a puppet about these nuts you fucking puppet make him faggot and then I'm the fuck out
of my face. Fuck me with like boobs.
and so I pushed against that's what I said like they're all losers they all they look listen the other like literally earlier today
Christine and Bita they were all talking about their cats and there's black RG on the panel like
Like you're you're a loser nigga your own panel with six cat ladies
Nobody gives a fuck about you black RG. You understand me now? If I ever met you in real life black RG
I will kill you
I would physically kill you
No, in real life. No
In my grasp in my grasp. Thank you
Wow, yeah, we have to like
To watch our weapon watch if I could get my hands if I could get my hands around black RG's little neck
I would never let go and just strangle him.
You understand?
In my-
No, no, no, no, give it your game.
Come on, come on, stop it, Joe.
Come on, let's not talk about it.
Immortal Crombat.
Let's not threaten anybody.
Stop it, Joe.
I was already threatened by this guy Tony today.
You know, he threatened me.
Can I say one thing to Jamie's Cowboys?
How about them Cowboys, baby?
How about them?
They had a nice draft.
I will say they had a nice draft, Jamie.
Come on, now.
about them
No, Jamie's means a lot to me. I'll always like Jamie. I knew Jamie before I even met your flannel wearing fucking ass like you
So calm down. I got a hold down good times. You know
Jamie is like a lover to me. Yeah, that's them. Oh my gosh, Jamie. What do you think about? Yeah, so back up so back off
Don't get all worked up so you know you can work them about
She said she's wearing her person's jersey in the bay.
No, one time I'd like RG, but I actually liked the other day.
I'd seen a clip.
It was RG versus Sam and I listened to the whole turkey.
I know, and they're, it was awesome.
It was actually RG.
Did you hear he was trying to get RG?
Well, one time he called me sloppy and I just, I took it the wrong way.
I'm sorry, psyche.
But one time he called me sloppy and I took it the wrong way.
So somebody asked me a question.
Why don't you like RJ?
And I gave him the answer.
You want to call me sloppy, boy?
Watch your mouth Archie. I really have nothing against him
I had to like go on a campaign everyone's just going nuts over like calling people PDF and stuff like that
And it's like even Alexander today, you know, she had this guy Ganville was like, you know
Who kind of styles himself PDF hunter or whatever and he admits like well, they're not really he's like well
You know, we just call it anybody under 18 now
Yeah, like you know anything involved anything under 18 is PDF
Basically, if you go to anybody, I'm not touching anybody, but if you go to anybody's
panel in this community, if you stay there for 15 minutes, you're going to hear the
P word or the, you're going to hear pedophile or kids, you're going to hear the word kids
are better.
If you stay there for 15 minutes, you're, that's how lame these fucking, it's not you.
Like Suggie, you're actually one of the last real motherfuckers out here, bro.
Don't give up, man.
Don't give up on yourself.
i'm not i'm not giving up i still have great friends like people that people can
out do you mind if i sing you a song real quick maybe don't mind down here it's a full house
to theme song voice bush loving code get it right you cut me right back down to size
sometimes it blows my mind
Oh, oh, that's that's the base and you love Scott Wildard's you little gay. Oh, that's the pitch mode. No, no, no, no
Are you gay? Suggie? Are you gay?
Hey, I think I still am. I'm not good. Just sound like it because you sound like it. Yeah, but we have another guest
Who's the surprise guest, okay? Here we go?
Let's be
I don't want to come back down from this clouds, Psyche is taking me on this tie-ye-ye-ye-ye-ye
It's beautiful and I don't want to come back down from this
Who's lamp it who the fuck was that lamp and just that what I was saying who the fuck would you happen?
You motherfucker
Who the fuck just lamp when I was singing my song
What up, man is happy Friday, nigga, what a what a fat boy
the
Look at the muscles, my muscles all fat, they go
Shut up you fat boy
Yo, take it for that picture bro
Oh my god
Oh, that's the first picture, wow
I'm gonna get Joe in less time
I caught you good nigga, I caught you good, I got your picture
Yo, when I was a dog, man, I saw she'll be one of my cartoon character
No, Joe, I'll fuck with you. I'll fuck with you, Joe. Don't take it serious.
I'm down, man.
Oh, I see a fish. Oh, I see a fish.
Crack, crack, crack, crack, crack, crack, crack.
Is that one? No, it's that one.
That was easy tonight this morning.
I haven't had any Modellos.
Hanging out at the the dawns. I guess Donald Duck, you know the dawns Donald Duck. Yeah, yeah, Donald Duck
Yeah, yo, do you remember to say that I remember when I was a kid my mama took me to a grocery store when I was like
We're a little kid and they had Donald. No, they said they had orange
With Donald Duck on it
It's like a mango color right your mango fuck. Yeah, exactly sucky. Thank you, man. So he's the one they gotta do fuck
Ducktales, you know what?
Each other for mom you yo
Yo, your name is literally lesbian. Let me talk to
Can you hear me psyche?
I hear you just loud and clear Joe
I think a lot of people that attack you when they were like in high school
They were like lonely losers and now that they're like old they get on panel and they like bully people
They're losers and they always will be you're a legend psyche. You understand me. Don't ever let those cowards bring you down
Don't ever let those pieces of shit break your day.
Thank you so much.
I mean, it's like, I'm trying not to, like, you know,
I'm not even trying, it's like, I'm just like ignoring,
like, you know, the silliness and like that.
Because, you know, I do have like a lot of great friends,
a lot of great supporters, and, you know,
and Kate's like, oh, well.
Here's one thing you're losing all your support. No one likes
anymore. You have three people in your chat. You know, I don't
care if I have three
I've seen an episode of Jerry Springer where they had to cut
the wall down to get a fat person out of their apartment.
That's literally what Kate is like, Kate, stop eating fucking
donuts and sugar all day. Maybe we'll be 900 fucking pounds,
you pig. So don't you dare come up and talk about psyche. Like
why don't you psyche you really let me fucking talk for one
second. Okay.
But you're gonna get mad that Kate says something you Kate is a fucking pig Kate is a fucking literal pig
And you're gonna get fucking like you're gonna work them about that
Wow, so I'm trying to sound like Sam and your retard
You let me talk bitch
Say shoo-woo-woo-woo-woo your fucking creak
He's there man
Where else you gotta say that boy knows you won't say that boy
But you
Well, I'm actually from Western Maryland, I'm not
I'm actually call me punky Brewster actually no walkie-pink
Pocky pick
Anybody remember punky Brewster?
Maybe the world I'm on that shit that show that show the point you wish to show
Hold on let me say your my favorite song show. You don't mind
It's a rare condition this day and age
What don't want any good news on the newspaper Bay?
Grand design some people say
Whatever lesbians
But there must be some magic
Yeah, see a gay guy who wouldn't know what we're singing. See like you. Yep. Say if anybody's getting interrupt us interrupt us gay boy
You gay boy bitch
What the hell did you just say to me, bitch?
You heard that, you fucking dirty, fucking dirty ass, okay?
You dirty ass, fuck off.
You look like good a mother
You son of a bitch
Ah, shut the fuck up asshole. I
Wish you would chew in a cyanide. I wish you would chew on a nut nigga. Oh my god
Okay, okay, you like what's that taste? I'm like, oh, I just slipped you a sign up
You know die a little bit die
Bitch you need to die a little better
You need to die a little bitch you need to die a little bitch
You just tell me to die that is so rude. Yeah
Yeah, you piggy boy
Sorry, sorry, this guy's very nice. Why are you getting mad?
Yo yo bro, what you getting man?
I'm just talking to you bro, I'm not sorry trust me
Yo bro, how you been doing? Yo Joe, how you been?
Yo, that serious? How you been doing? How you been doing?
Well, I'm assuming good until you came on the panel
I was doing a great job at you
Nah, at least see you for a hundred minutes
I had to mess with you bro
Nah, it's all good in games
Do you mind if I smoke a cigarette?
Well, don't call your mom my girl. Don't call your mom my girl boy
Make I'll tuck you in
Where's my crack play that what's your girl?
She's probably at your mother's house.
Oh, my mom is not around.
They go, she's dead.
She's in the cemetery.
She's in my mom's house.
Very crazy.
How many people in this panel's moms are dead like beat his mom's day correct Q45
I don't know you don't ever call me your bro
I
I don't want you to do me a favor. You good look in the mirror and look at yourself and that picture me
I try your psyche though psyche though psyche those you little bird-ass dude
Don't yeah, don't call me Bronsburg. That is a that is a good
Yo, that's a penguin
But you know, the Sugar Ray just played it up in Redondo and they were just here
playing
I just want
Put your arms around
Joe Joe what a fight will be Joe. Why you want to beat me up Joe? Why you want to beat me up for?
There's one song about you bless. It's like I'm like
Oh, Joe's a lesbian
What the fuck yeah, thank you. I see that's a compliment. Thank you, but
If I was just being the last the last one see I was like
Can I say old whore
So I'm gonna tire to be there
No, you'll make me throw up nigga. Well, we're all gagged don't go gagging yourself like this nigga can't even
Yeah, but I wish I've ever met you. I wish you would have that
My
No, man. Oh, okay. I'm gonna eat shit, by the way. You're shit
No, no, you don't shit motherfucker. I never ate a lesbian shit before
Actually, no, you ain't got shit. You ain't dog shit. They got
We don't shit cash it
Nice, I'm like this guy actually I'd like this guy
Okay, you just said I eat cats
That was actually rude. That was very rude
Yo easy, were you wet easy?
Easy wheezy
Yeah, when I do go shopping it or like there's a Gershwin
Yo, you have to take
Whole store
Oh, you wrote what does it say you run, New York? Oh God this
Man run, New York
That's my mama
I
Haven't been doing your sake. Yeah, you've been doing man. I've been okay. I've been okay
My haters is Matt is Matt haters. Yeah. Yeah, and I'm not I saw I saw the earlier the little video you did earlier
Thank you. It's a weird psyche when like people come on your paddle and they're like lesbians like this fucking
Yo, Joe, why you so Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe
Well, why are you talking top?
You ever notice when these black people man, they're like you saw
You stupid motherfucker ain't black bro. You taking about
You know what? This woman, Crystal Ann, is insane. I was gone half a year last year from
I got sick around May. I'm without a sepsis. I was in ICU for about a week and a half.
I had like eight days to live and and I had no listen and then I had to go to rehab to learn to walk again because
Let me talk Joe. Okay
YouTube and everything for a while I was trying to get my life back and I didn't get discharged till early September
Through that time Crystal used that Nancy. I don't know if you talked to her. She talks to Barry
Um to contact me because she was already turning on Nancy for some reason and somebody else was involved
It was just a bunch of bullshit. Here. She was blowing me up and I see you when I'm over there fighting for my life
You know, she's crazy
And she's trying to and I'm the one that cut her off and if you look at my videos
You'll see that she was blowing me up from all kinds of
What is your name?
what is your name sweetie remember it was the other day i got on with you ian x remember
you were on it ian x yeah okay but anyway psyche she's crazy okay let me talk she's crazy
right now psyche i mean i'll go on panel with you and alex she's stalking alex
I've been out of the loop. I just had to rescue this cat that I had to get fixed and vaccinated.
All of that, you know, I do real life, but this bitch is 24 seven online. She's had so many 51 50s
done on her. All she does is stalk us and throw her names into the bus.
Trista is so crazy
And she came on she came on to take Bita thunder that's what it was she wants Bita gone
She's insane and I've never liked her. I'm the one that blast or blasted her out for the truth. Look at my other videos
Look at the video on the video about how we called her out when Renee on top who was DX
busted her out for the fake charges against a guy named Vienna who was only renting a room from her.
Look at those videos in Chelsea you saw Chelsea listen listen to her
they she's crazy crystal and is crazy she's a fucking stalker and she wouldn't leave me alone
look at the call log that i posted in her calls for me yeah and and i just want you to know jamie's
cabboys in the chat that's a different jamie this is oh no no i know that's not the jamie that she
Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe
It's really insane and I've been busy psyche. I think you even knew that cuz I'm kind of
Yeah, shut up Joe damn stop drinking damn you do this all the time
Okay
Yeah, he's crazy
Miss hockey she came on to take beat it down. She thinks she's really queen. She's very narcissistic
Her family won't have shit to do with her. I have that proof and if I have to post that I will
I was leaving it alone because I do real life. I was sick of her calling
Please look through my videos. You don't see the proof that she even tried to contact me from different
Discords three group chats
three IG accounts and then telling me oh it's not you it's the chats that's starting to make us fight
look at that that's she's insane and that's my proof that you're she's running her mouth saying
i'm calling her no i did try to call her uh the other day to tell her stop saying my name i'm doing
real life you know we just said i just saved this cat got a tree i'm doing real life and she's on 24
Yeah, she's crazy. She's going too far. And uh, I mean she's
Oh, they're watching
Yeah, I mean it's like I'm not a lot. I mean I said hello in her chat one time to somebody and then it's like
I was just immediately banned perma banned there. So I'm not even allowed to have a voice but then she complains that alexandra
You know put her chat on private one day because crystal lands whole chat came over to alexander's and started harassing everybody crazy
See that's her whole life is the internet. She look at some of the videos on her
She has real high anxiety out in public and she can't be around people not only is she socially awkward, but you can hear her going
Like that. It's just really weird like, you know, she was trying to get cue to go on a date with her and she was like
Yeah, he turned it down. Yeah, he said he said if I turned down psyche, do you think you have a chance? I
Know right. It's just insane. She's she's so crazy and I'd called the police on her and there's another case against her
She's so full of shit and then somebody said that when I was out I came home and they call me goes where you been
I said I just can't came home
And he said that she went live and deleted it, but she went live and said that I was arrested
She's so crazy. She's obsessed with us
Nancy doesn't want shit to do with her. I don't either
She was screaming on the phone like she couldn't stand to get lose me. We weren't friends. It's like I don't want any communication with her
I couldn't stand her
No, not reality Nancy. It's another Nancy that was part of the orange group.
Did you ever hold one of, did you hold, did you ever hold baby Oliver?
No, no, she had to buy a baby Oliver. I've never met the woman. You know, she sold baby Oliver and the twins
Yeah, she thought they were real babies for her and then Aaron Carter, you know, he called the police on her
She harassed him. I talked to Melanie and she calls her a nightmare though
You know, she just got the money for the hoodies and she said she tell her some crazy story
She did I have an old DM where she sent saying that Ganville wanted to kill her
And this was from five years ago. She's insane.
I guess she loves good guy gamble now and gamble I guess you know
Alexander exposed today about how gamble you know kind of has been lying about people like you know in order yeah
I saw that yeah, I saw that yeah
He groomed a kid named Daniel that was in the news and then that Branigan lady. Yes
He's not supposed to have a channel on YouTube right, but there was another person and he rest and then oofy
Remember they have the clip of him instructing him to do the SWAT
Right. I mean, it's crazy. I kind of like almost like, you know, I'm just trying to kind of stay away from that group
I have like a lot of like my own stuff going on right now. And it's like, you know
Yeah, they've been slandering me like, you know
Like, you know, just like but a lot of people have, you know
But I think that these people are cuckoo for cocoa puffs kind of people that they're just like, you know going with popular
Thing when they call everyone PDFs. I mean it literally everybody like literally every single person here
They people have called that right? I mean if you
That here is like you're not you haven't been part of the panel verse because everyone literally gets called that and it's yeah
But I mean she's just a mental case. It's like damn, you know go touch grass and do real life
And she she doesn't even know her next-door neighbor
There was a dog running loose and I said is it belong to your next-door neighbor? Oh, I don't know and I said well
Who can you can you ask him? I don't know them. It's like that's weird like she doesn't do real life
She doesn't touch grass. I you know, and I'm the one that busted her out along with Renee on top
About the fake charges against that Vienna guy look at all my videos. You'll see the truth all the videos on her
Just the ones on her and I don't know why why you weren't able to post your link today
But you should you're a mod you should be able to oh, yeah, I could do it didn't yeah
I don't know it didn't let me do that
But yeah, I just been busy the last few days so I hadn't been really watching anything till somebody told me about her bullshit
She's just very obsessed and I never cared for her. You know, I knew she was a liar
Um, and everybody's been careful her because every time she calls us all she wants us to fight with each other
It's always this person says this about you look at my videos and you'll see because recently she was saying
Oh, it's all Nancy and Jamie in the chat and Bruno agrees with me. Look at it
How crazy she is and now she's saying I'm actually with her
I have something to talk about, you know, it's your first show and
Yeah, it's crazy. Yeah, but he's going along with it the guy that sent 25 guys to her house when he craig listed her
Right. I mean, you know, yeah. Well, that same thing happens to me. I'm being craig listed, too
And I know it's a big big. It's like a little I had this lady come today for two hours for a week
She drove two hours for a weed whacker. She's 75 years old
You know a Hispanic woman down from downtown LA. She drove over here
And because some guy some idiot asshole is trying sending people to my house and not to bang on my door
They he says go bang on the door, but we rule out. I'm hard of hearing and stuff like that
It just yeah harass me. And so I'm you know, I understand this crazy harassment. It's yeah
It's great. Oh, and then one more thing I need to add that she's a liar
Yeah, she said that she gives Bruno money so he can sit on her panel with her in the beginning because she was scared
That people come attack her because she's got a bad reputation
Yeah, and she said she gives him about 30 or $35 because he likes weed and he smokes weed
There was something about a Facebook or whatever that was posted and she said give him some money for that
He'd help with that and I did
And then I gave him some extra for his birthday.
That's all I did.
It was an extra $25 for a birthday,
but she's the one over there.
And I had to record her.
And I have all the texts I'm gonna do videos of to post.
She's insane.
And she didn't respect my boundaries.
Like when I was in the physical therapy,
learning to walk,
and we had to do the workout on machines.
She kept blowing me up like she didn't care. It's always drama at home at that time
Like she doesn't respect people's boundaries, and it was just too much as soon as we'd hang up
She'd call again. Oh, oh, yeah
I mean it was and then she was always calling the police on these guys that she invites over to her place
And I've got videos of that that she sent me with a police at her door. Oh, yeah
Really crazy and you know, yeah, I would how do you get rid of that?
I guess with the police because she cried a couple years ago when the police called her and you know to stop harassing me
And I'm gonna and it's gonna happen again, and then she freaks out
But she's insane she even involved her as aunt. We're being re-streamed right now. Oh, yeah, that's fine
I don't care at least I'm telling the truth. I just want her to leave me the f alone
But wait watch all the videos and how she contacting me from
group chats and three accounts on IG and saying, oh, it's a chat trying to get us to fight.
It's Nancy and Jamie, you know, and she's trying to communicate with all of us and we're
done with her.
I don't understand why I'm allowed to do her show or to defend myself.
That's all she does is get on 24-7 to restream other people, but that's a truth and look
at all my videos and yes, the police are going to get in contact with her because she's
Never cared for her. I busted her out for the lies that she said on Beanna and Chelsea and look at those videos
And that what came from Renee on top who said I could share that it was a fake
Court thing that she did and her dad had to pay a thousand dollars
Okay, well I'm gonna jump off now because I gotta finish doing something, but thank you. Okay. All right. I'll talk to you later
All right. Bye. Bye. Bye
Okay, well, I'm back. Okay. How are we guys doing? I'm, uh,
I was putting the finishing touches on a video, um, but uh,
well, thank you INX for coming on and sharing. I mean, I'm not involved
in like a lot of this drama. Um, I just like, you know, and just having
it on my show. I mean, I do like, like, like people come on and speak. Um,
I don't want to, I don't want to, you know,
Increase the increase the drama or like you know, there's enough going on right now
But uh, yeah, I am banned on that show so I don't know like if you feel free to you know, restream me and everything
But it's kind of interesting. Okay, but um, so hopefully everyone's doing good in the chat
I'm just putting the finishing touches on something that I'll be
Premiering in a little bit, but maybe anyone wants to come up. You're welcome up
You know, but I do recommend you check out IP to wiki info channel and also
IRL news time there's been some interesting developments and you know
the you know Alexander broke a few a
Few new stories, and so I think that you might be interested in checking some of those out
And so anyway, so hopefully everyone's doing good tonight
Let me see. Let me we'll check out the chat and see how the chat's doing and
Let's see. I'm fine. It's okay. How's everybody quag? It'll be also easy. We'll be up in a few
Yeah, I mean, I really don't mind being re-streamed
You know, it's a guess up to the creator's discretion, but I do think you know if uh, you know, it shouldn't be like banned from
Conversation if you're gonna be streaming
Um, but yeah, it does seem like there's been some interesting developments
So check out all his honors channels, you know, definitely
She is like right on the cutting edge of a lot of this stuff. Um, so hopefully everyone's doing good. Um
Let me see. Okay. So, um, I'm having a little dinner right now. I have a couple
Of my harder harder eliminates her mangoes
Got the new phone today things are you know things go wrong and things go right and that's like I want to thank the people that really
Haven't helping me out
You know and they knew they knew who they are and I just want to shout out to them
Say I love you. Okay. And so
How's my?
Okay, this is almost done. Okay, so
Yeah, it's a little bit, you know, and maybe people just ran over there or whatever. I know people run back and forth
You know, maybe the state people feel safe for talking in some places in other places
You know what it's like I do I do I will stand up from for my from my people here and
Don't let people like, you know
Scare you into submission or scare you into not talking or scare you from a staying wave
I never would say don't go to this person's chat. Don't go to that person's chat
It's really the kind of lame that you know, some people have been doing that. Oh, don't donate money to this person
Don't do that like there's any in their business, right?
But people seem to be so still so free to like, you know slander to fame and then hide their hand
And kind of thing and it's like the same old games
I think you know the same things happen to Jesus like you know not to compare myself to Jesus
But I'm saying that you know, it's these are historical things. These are the things that go back thousands of years
the gang stalking the
targeted harassment
The TI kind of stuff
And it gets it gets sad, you know, and it's like and then also people are like calling me
Oh defender of this person that person when they and they have, you know
donated like
But I heard thousands of dollars to people that even have, you know
documented done far worse and so
Not to call anybody out, you know, I'm not trying not here to like, you know
start a hate train or anything like that.
I want people to have a place
they can go to defend themselves.
that they can feel safe to.
And it's like, and so,
disrespect the rules in my chat.
Everything should be fine.
Okay, I'm gonna start.
So, I think I should have this video ready for us to watch in just a few, and this one's
a good one.
Okay, it's going to be a good one, I promise you.
And okay, so this is just putting the finishing touches on this, okay.
But anyway, yeah, it's been an interesting time and let's just say like I do believe in karma
I do believe in that the truth will come out truthful prevail. I'm a big believer in truth and
Truth-telling and the real story because there's so much that is exaggerated. There's so much
and it's the internet so it's like oh it's okay to exaggerate because it's the internet no it's
really not and it's like you really are putting people's lives at stake and stuff when you do
some of this slander and I know people are just these it's like not pdf hunters it's clout hunters
it's clout chasers and it's like you know people that just want attention for their own you know
Tell the truth, right, right, but it's like when it's like when it's built on lies and destroying other people's lives
That's kind of sick to me and I don't understand why
It seems to be that some of these people are just getting a pass for that when other people are just you know, like that, you know
silence into oblivion which is a sad thing to me and so I will always be
standing up for truth and justice and I believe that's the American way okay
American or not and some people might be from different countries and stuff I
think that we all believe in and truth okay so and I will tell the truth I will
tell the truth even if it's unpopular I will be happy to tell the truth okay so
I do have this almost ready.
Okay.
I'm pretty excited to share this with you.
Oh, just take another minute or two.
So.
I just hope everyone's doing great out there.
I want to thank everybody that has stood by me
during this time, because I know it's like,
it is, you know, I have people like, you know,
I see people like I've had mods
that are being threatened by other people.
I would never threaten anybody's mods about, you know,
for being in my, in somebody else's chat or anything.
Everyone's free to go where they want to go.
It's like, people have freedom.
It's like, I don't understand why people feel so free
to try to scare people into, oh, don't go here
or you're protecting this.
Like everyone can be friends with who they want to be friends with everyone. I mean, it's like
You know, it's like and everyone can make the rules for their own show and everyone everyone can you know
Hide who they want to everyone can have platform who they want to I have no problem with anybody doing any of that
It's like, you know, I just asked those like people tell the truth
I mean basically just tell the truth and it's like that is like so. Oh, there's my cat
Oh, I guess I'm guess who's in here pie is in here
The black cat I think pies in here here. It's kind of me. Oh, there he is. Yeah pies in here
See if you can see pie here. I'm gonna show you guys. I can hi pie. Hi pie pie
So pie is tricks his brother. Okay. Here we go. I just want to show you pie. He's coming in
He came in right now. Okay, I'm gonna turn
There he is right there here
See him right there. He's been the vacuum right there. See it. There he is. Hi pie pie
I was born March 14th 3.14. So he is oh, that is called pi day. Okay
Okay, so you're ready for the premiere, I got the premiere for you. There's pie right there. There's your pie
Here's my new premiere guys. You get the exclusive you see it here first, okay?
enjoy
Okay, I hope you do enjoy
Here you go guys
Thanks for watching, and I'll see you in the next one.
And souls through digital dreams
Con fashion booths became social feats
Now predators harvest emotion leaks
I watched weak men drown in attention
Rain trading in our kingdoms for five seconds
Fame day said be honest
I opened the gate now strangers
Wearing my secrets like a king
it stayed. Thank you. Oh my god. You like the song? Thank you. Yeah, there's Rudy. I'm gonna
see Rudy. There's Rudy right there. I'm sorry. There's Rudy. Hey, dude. He's looking over the
and I guess he I guess he ran out. I ran out. But you know, I'm glad he's back here. Oh,
I don't know. It's focusing away from me. There we go. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. I'd like the song.
Thank you. All right. Those based those songs on teachings of Machiavelli actually, was actually
I don't think necessarily was just trying to like educate the prince or whatever, but I think was
Yeah, he's always on high alert, huh? Where is he? I think he was trying to try and to like actually
Maybe the more like everybody
About these about these sticks, you know, I don't think he was just teaching the prince. There he is. Hi rude
Come down and say hi. Hi. Hi, sir
Hi, you're meowing. Hi. He's a little weak meow
There's a lot of his meow goes guys
He's 18 years old. He's a little bit older of an older cat
but
He's a very sweet cat. He likes today. I got into the covers with me. There's been low. I had a little a little fit. She's
Lola's not in the best mood right now. I can touch you looking away. Oh, la
Yeah, we're easy. We're just a good cat
Good cat he's very very soft. He has like brush marks in him
Hi rude. Oh
There you go
So anyway
You know like I said, I don't need a I don't need a hundred people in here
I have 15 great people in here like I've had today like I haven't had even like one troll really
I don't think I've had to hide one person
Tonight, you know, and so it does seem like you know once you the trash almost takes itself out and so yeah
Hi
Little motor sound I watched Saints this morning like saying, you know Saints on the RV with like I guess chicken Andy and
It was there I think they were fighting and stuff and they're all in there
Underwear on the RV this morning. It's kind of funny
I don't know who's keeping up with that with Saints and chicken Andy and stuff like that. It's kind of entertaining a little bit
It's pretty entertaining
Yeah, so anyway, but I do have a great I have a great group of people here
I'm very blessed to have you guys, you know, and I just want to thank you
You know, and it's like I'll thank you by like, you know giving you as long as I can I'll give you a place to hang out and
You know as long as people are respectful and like, you know, like, you know
Sometimes, you know, I have to have a talk with some people and like, you know
Put them on put them on game a little bit because I do like to have a more fun
respectful chat and not
Sonico art. I mean so many people are there's a lot of hateful chats. I noticed there's a lot of hateful chats
They're just like, you know about there's bullies. Oh
Oh, you yawned you had a big yawn. Hi. Hi, sir
You're not coming
He's very soft.
Hi, you're a little soft cat.
Kind of like, he's like, what?
He's like, oh, you're spanking me.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Hey, there's Lenore, Lenore.
Come here.
Come here, Lenore, come here too.
Hi, oh, he's meowing.
He's just meowing at me.
Hi, hi, sir.
Little head against me. Hi, baby. Hi, baby
Isn't he a good-looking cat though? He's a good-looking cat. Oh
Oh, oh
His elder years he loves his attention. Yeah. Yeah, I got him last year, you know a family friend
Was like I'm gonna I'm gonna move and I'll be out a lot with my with my boyfriend and
You know, I don't know if he's gonna want to move and
You know be alone in this new house and I'm afraid to run away and stuff and she's like will you take him and I was like
Oh, I was like I have a lot of cats, but yes, I'll I'll take him and
She brought him over one night. You may you join come on up Joe and
And she came she could she like put some like calming treats in in a in a little carrier
He jumped right in the carrier for the treats, you know
And then she called and she's like, what do I do?
What do I do?
He's in the carrier.
And I said, well, bring him over here.
I was like, you got him, like bring him over here.
She's like, are you sure?
I was like, yes.
And then he came over and she was crying and she said,
she said, I think I'm a bad cat mom.
Cause it's like, you know, he's, you know, he's so old
and you know, I'm like, you know, bring him somewhere else.
But I was like, I was like, he's going to have a great life
and he's going to be happy.
What's up Jack?
it was
I
The one thing I will say if you don't mind if you mind if I say one thing real quick
I think these losers like salmon and beta like they were lowly in high school
But they were like losers got picked on so now that they're 50 years old now
They can have their own panel and they can have their little group thinking that their little bully panel
You know what you're gonna bully me Sam and
Yeah, and they're such bully. I mean there are such bullies and it's like and it's like if you see them in real life
It's like wow, it's like, okay. What the fuck did you ever do wrong?
You never did nothing wrong psyche and these cock suckers like oh sucky says sucky's that
I'm dirty. I'm dirty. I'm bad at tarot cards. I'm I'm just I mean it's like they have so many things to say about me
When I've been like really I was really the worst thing they can say much like oh, he got dirty fingernails
Probably because he was up beat us
Dirty puss every day
Look at this thickness now boy. Oh clean it'll clean itself
They look nice. I imagine. I'm cleaner. They're a green machine. It's very clean.
Yeah, I'm bad at some points because I dig through tobacco and stuff like that. And you
know, I tend to like, you know, I, I, I, this is tobacco, my bomb and stuff like that.
Every once in a while, you got to light up a cigarette butt. But you know what, sucky? At
least you don't beg for like somebody buy me cigarettes. At least you dig through your
cigarette bus and light a cigarette. But you're not a creepy fuck like beat in salmon. You don't
It's like, oh, somebody might be cigarettes.
You'll like the last cigarette, but you have.
Well, yeah, I know.
You know what, I shout to your long hair.
I love your long hair.
You sexy beast.
Thank you, Joe.
Well, thank you so much.
Yeah, I do have a thing for you.
No, because I'm just doing, I'm trying to do a crystal answer.
Like, why are you kissing Psyche's ass?
Are you kidding me?
Because he's my best friend.
Don't you ever fucking tell me why I'm talking to psyche cuz I fucking love it. That's why I fucking thought if you might have
I do me too. Oh no, and when I'm done smoking a cigarette, I'm gonna do me with you. Thank you
Well, I appreciate that Joe. You know, it's like and I know it's so fucked up
Why do I like psyche cuz he's the fucking best
The fuck do you mean?
Like, do you know what I'm trying to say?
They're trying to make us hate you.
Well, they're trying to make us,
they're trying to conform us.
They ain't gonna conform me.
Right, they're the bully group.
It's like, look at that weirdo.
Like, Psyche's a weirdo,
and he hangs out with weird people,
and everyone in this area is weird.
And it's like, you know what?
I don't mind being weird.
I don't mind hanging out with-
No, Psyche, you're the opposite of that.
You're the coolest nigger.
Oh, sorry.
Oh.
You're the coolest guy out there.
No, you're the coolest.
I was so embarrassed when they said, like,
why do you like saying, I was like, why don't I like him?
I was like, you know what I said to him?
I was like, I don't like him.
I love him.
They're like, oh, you're banned.
Thank you.
They banned me because I said, I love you.
They banned you.
Okay, well, I mean, there's lame.
I mean, it's like pretty much just lame.
Like, I'm not gonna ban anybody for saying they like Crystal Ann.
I would say they should have better taste, but.
uh i mean i'm not gonna like i'm not gonna like you know like i've seen a lot of girls in my life
but chrysaline will be one that i would ever touch with a ten foot pole
you understand me? I know I mean she has a picture her avatar looks like the princess diaries or
something like I've seen a lot of good looking women. Chris Owain is not one of them. You understand
Chris Owain is not one of them. Gamble was like, you know, oh, she's he's like, well,
you're gonna find a great guy, Chris. Well, it's not gonna mean me, but you'll find a great guy.
I don't judge people by their voice, but the second I want to tell you something so I get
I want you to hear me. I really want you to hear me.
The second I heard Gambo's voice, I think that guy's a creep.
I can just tell right now that that guy's a fucking creepy.
like you check his hard drive, the guy has child porn.
I know, some of these people, you should check their hard drive,
but he's labeled himself as a PDF hunter,
but his only targets were Zaya and Brandon, you know,
those were his names.
You know, what creeps even label yourself a PDF hunter?
Oh, a PDF, like you can.
Right, I would think so, I would think so,
someone that's like, you know, gonna put themselves as like,
I'm the, you know, I'm like, yeah, okay.
I remember the movie Dennis the Manus when Mr. Wilson had that plant growing and like
it only blew one time every three years and like Dennis the Manus ruined it.
I don't know if it's a corpse flower but I do know about the corpse flower and I know
that that is like there's a corpse flower.
Is that a beer right here?
Is that a beer that I hear?
It's a Cherry Hard Lemonade.
Lucky this is an open Bob wiser. Look at me. This is
Good to see you. Oh, I said Alex. Thank you Alex at least Alex is real
Yeah, I'm so tired of these fucking fake streamers like beta and crystal in like let's get some realness up in here
Let's get a little real
Right, it's time to stop being a polite and start getting real real world
And also what I really appreciate about Alex is that you know, she had some streams today where she you know
Kind of updated her stance on a few issues and it's like yeah people that are willing to like you know say maybe
Yeah, like you know, I really do admire that and
I really recommend, check out IPTWiki Info, and check out the IRL News Time, and check out Alexander Mayer's, and, uh, you know...
Yeah, I see something, sir.
Yeah, I see something, too.
Yes, when those cock suckers said why are your friends was like I say you know what I'd rather go back to suckies
Than even meal panel you fucking losers. So you know what? I'm right where I belong nigga. I'm right where I belong
You are you are and you're welcome here always and it's like and I just like appreciate
Have to say that like our RG and Q and and J-Dog and
Yeah, but I came up trying to form on me came up trying to like, you know
not even like no respect. And I've had them all. I've had them on for over a year to talk
their shit and say whatever they want. And they're going to treat me like that because
it is agree on some issue about certain people. I mean, it's like, we don't have to agree on
everything. You know, people can have their own opinions about things, but it's like,
you know, but then it's just to try to destroy me for that. And it's like, you know, it's
just why am I friends with Suggie? Because I love him. He's a good guy.
thank you like you know what sometimes psyche it's hard to find real people up here nowadays
all these fucking creeps it's just hard to find the real one and you know what why are my friends
with psyche because he's real go and rub your hair I think I'm over my hair yeah and you know what
and that's what I am I'm a real person and I um you know um
You know, sometimes I'm a little bit messy.
Sometimes I'm not, I'm not perfectly put together.
Sometimes I don't, I don't say the perfect thing
or like, you know, know what's going on exactly,
but I am real and it's like, and so like me or not,
like I am, I show myself on, you know, and it's like,
like my-
May I respond to that?
May I respond to what you're saying?
Maybe I'm not perfect.
I might not be perfect, but you know what?
I'm perfect enough for him, a best friend right here.
And if I'm good enough for psyche, then I'm good enough for anybody.
If I'm good enough for my boys psyche, then I'm good enough for anybody.
So anybody that has a promise psyche, come and talk to me.
Right Joe. Well, thank you so much. And that's really touching. I do really appreciate I
Really appreciate the people that you know and and like a lot of people have given me another chance and a lot like I know
Like a lot of people and it's like I do appreciate
Like a second chance. It's like, you know, and I always you know
I'm a very forgiving person too and it's like and so I do appreciate people that
are willing to forgive and like, you know, and it's like, you know, basically it's how people
approach me as like, I'll treat people how they treat me. And a lot of people got their start
off your streams, like a lot of people got their start off for you. And now that they're like,
oh, they don't care about second or more, make a comeback to your roots. Come back to your roots.
Right, and I brought a lot of together too. I brought a lot of people together
When I started my show to go to different communities and I
Channel and I would promote and so I got people from different communities and so many of them have
Left me in the dust but they and then they are friends your panels are like love and other people's panels are hate
You are a good guy
The whether you like it or not, I'm gonna go to my grave. Say you're a good guy. Thank you
And you're gonna get good too, and you know, and it's like you
A little bit of you're a little bit rough around the edges. I like that. I like and I like how really you are
And stuff like that because you never porn bomb me, you know, or you know, it's all your wiener maybe once or something like that
Yeah, I don't think you're trying to show me.
Now you're lying.
Now you're making those stories.
OK, I'm making you a story.
Where was that first movie?
You were holding a bag of Cheetos in your lap.
That's what happened.
That's what it was. Oh, Cheeto beer when he was underage. I need I need I need dick so bad. I'm
going to buy a 19 year old guy beer. It's not Bita like Bita. We know you love your cast,
but like you get dick. You buy an underage guy beer. Wow. That is fucking so fucked up. That is
it's like and even then it's like you know and no one really cares about that kind of thing but
they're going to scream about other people and like judge other people for doing the same things
that maybe they have to I mean it's like and you know nobody's really perfect and everything
but it's like I don't think unless you people have hurt somebody that uh
can I ask you a question it's like do you remember one time Samman remember Samman used to clip
people and like talk about their clips
I think that's why Bita became friends with Sam and like,
oh, please don't clip me and talk about my drunk ass.
Like Bita, we all know you're a fucking drunken retard,
fucking idiot.
Okay, well, you know, it's like,
I mean, happy birthday to her and everything, whatever.
I mean, it's like, I'm banned from her show.
Happy 55th, happy 55th, you old fucking cunt.
I'm sorry, I'm really a little too much.
It's okay, it's okay.
I kind of like what I'm hearing.
Sometimes it's like, there's some things I'm hearing.
When I turn 20, I get over my birthdays.
Imagine being 50 and still celebrating your birthday.
Like, we get nobody to think about you.
And we don't mean, it's like, you know what?
It's all about how cool you are,
because there's people that are in there.
There's, there's people in their seven, I think Karen might be in their, in her seventies and she's cool as fuck, you know, and, and, you know, so it doesn't matter what age you are, it's like, you know, it's like the age is really like a.
age is really just it's about the motion of the ocean. You can be as old as you were, but it's
about the motion. It's about the way you act. I'd like to think that I'm a good friend of you,
Suggie. Am I right? You're a good friend of me. And Joe, you've been here since the beginning,
like you really, you've been here since the beginning of the show almost basically when you
started having over panels, one of the first people, and maybe I was like, you know, and maybe
if I- Can you look, Suggie, can you imagine Crystal Ann said to me, why are you talking to Suggie?
You're a fucking fish-eyed loser.
Suckie is the man.
And you be lucky to be on Suckie's panel,
you fucking gay guys.
And I allowed her on my panel before,
and I was respectful to her.
Do you mind if I be a cigarette?
You mind if I smoke a cigarette?
I don't mean to ever talk to you, but go ahead,
all right, go ahead, talk to me.
You're fine, you're absolutely fine.
But I said hello in her chat,
and I did nothing.
Disrespectful or anything to her. She just doesn't like what I believe or what I who I have on my show or something like that
So I'm like basically silenced
And then she's complaining about
Alexander's chat when I was on when she sends her her whole chat over to harass
Alexandra's show and then Alexandra's says hey, you know what?
This is distracting from the the interview and the conversation we're having so I'm just gonna turn off my channel
there's just so offended that they can't have a voice but it's like they're so happy to take away anybody else's voice
oh we did have a voice we're so offended like ugh like I turned 51 last week
Bita you're an old fucking cunt we don't care you old bitch
okay well and Bita is like an old she acts like an old lady you know and it's like
but I know who does and never Christine comes up there and sweepy it's like an old lady fast like
Because it's like, you know, really it's like you're just as young as you as you kind of like feel inside of you act but they're acting like
they're like, you know, in their nineties or something like that.
I noticed that when Bita went live today, she only had like 49 people in her chat.
Like the viewers are getting less.
Like people are getting tired of it.
Like we're getting tired of your old same shoe story.
Yeah, look, there's 48 people in my chat right now.
There's 48 people in my chat.
And so that's, that's a W.
Because, you know, Bita will usually have it.
Hey, we have a guest coming up.
Let's say hello to Joni Belong.
Aw.
Hey
I just want to make a quick comment without pissing you off
Joe I've been real supportive of you being positive for psyche
But can you use back on the what we call ageism because trust me you don't not everybody's broad stroke
So you're saying it and I get it
Wow
If you really, if you really see the good in this show stream owner right here, you wouldn't
be just saying that kind of mean mom shit.
Another guest.
Whoa.
And that guest is sexy.
That guest is sexy.
Well, everyone's sexy up here tonight.
Tonight's the sexy panel.
Jesus.
Well, I'm so not used to people turn the camera off.
Like, at least a good looking woman has her camera on.
That's sexy to me.
Uh-huh.
Come on. Oh, whatever dude. Are you still talking goodbye loser? Okay?
She seems like a nice person. I know she seemed pretty nice. Goodbye
How you doing Alex?
I'm good. I'm good. I enjoyed your show today, by the way. I enjoyed I enjoyed I
Tried to cover everything. I needed to today was one of those days. I did my regular work. I did this
Now I'm talking to you. I even did a little exercise today. I'm feeling good, but um, you have a glow on
You know, uh
There
some people are jerks right you know they're just yeah I agree
Yeah, I know I think I know who you're talking about. I don't know if it's like that CA woman like, you know
I think that honestly, I think that she's mentally stunted. I can't take anything. Yes. Thank you. She's mentally retarded
Yeah, well that
Yeah, because he was my favorite one let him on the panel or the jack is like
Why do you like psyche like in stuff like that? I mean, it's like pretty
I said, I'll like it. I'm gonna put you backstage for a little bit. Okay. I'm gonna have a chance here
So how are you doing today?
I'm doing actually pretty good.
I got a new phone today.
My phone.
Yay, that's good.
Yeah, okay, we have Joni back and yeah, so I got.
Okay, hi Joni.
Hey, how you doing?
Nice to meet you bud, buddy.
Oh my god, I'm trying to change my picture because I I don't know how I have a bird
Well, I have
No, listen, I have a bird bird. No shush. I have a bird nest that
like us randomly I live in an apartment showed up and had a mama bird and it like like like life
was right throughout so my door while I'm busy making plans in my head right and and then like
the other night they were live and I try to like live stream it I didn't know how to so I put it
up there but I want to try to change that picture I'm kind of like a dork when it comes to
Yeah, there's some Robins, like the Red Robins came.
She's like a little, like a, like she's a balcony, right?
And so she has the ornament of a balcony
and a bird put a nest there.
And so she was like, what does this mean?
There's like, mama birds appear
and she wanted to go through the symbolism of-
Well, yeah.
It's gotta mean something, doesn't it?
Robins do have a spiritual meaning.
I don't know what, but I'm going to look it up right.
I know, right?
I have a wreath outside that's like with some sunflowers on it and
I have a balcony and I usually feed birds like and I'm really big on the red cardinals. That's
real spiritual to me. Like, you know, they always say like your past loved ones signs and all that
kind. I'm all that kind of way. And then I noticed this Robin kind of a puffy chest bird with a worm
in its mouth. And I was sitting on like, why isn't he run or him her running away when I'm like out
there. And then all of a sudden I looked up and noticed, wait, there's a little nest that I can't
they don't have like hands right and knees and bones and joints they have
little paws or little feet they make a fucking they freaking make a nest how
do they do it and I know I don't want to get deep in my thoughts but we take
shit for granted right how can that happen and then the mama was up there
and I have a cat that goes out there and anyway long story short I felt some
kind of weird you're talking about motherhood and all that I felt some kind
weird way, like you're so close, like you're one wall away
from inside my apartment. And I'm responsible, but I didn't
ask for this. But yet did I? You know, like all these weird
random thoughts. By the way, I'm Joni. That's this is like,
this is Joni, the goofy one. But nice to meet you. Nice to
meet you too. Well, Robbins, apparently, spiritually mean
messenger of renewal, joy and comfort, representing rebirth.
So do you are you going into like a new phase of life?
Well, it's kind of hard to talk about that when someone just when somebody just ages isn't me out the door
It's like just called me like eight years old
I know
Stupid and then like in the chat I like totally compliment. Thank you for being nice and supportive
Like how could you so good and nice and yet broad stroke everyone so a woman that's 50
50 could be a woman that's 80 or a woman that's 80 could be really a soul that's young.
So like, I don't like that, but this is our world we live in.
So shut up, Joni, but I hate when they do it.
Like I'm not even supposed to be on the internet.
I don't even know I got brought up in this.
Yes, you are.
You and I are probably about the same age.
I'm 47.
Right.
Well, older than you, my dear.
But I mean, and I, and you know, you always talk like you're so old and I'm like, stop
it.
I always told.
Well, I'm gonna say John.
stop doing that because
it's it's all perception like when you turn 30 it's old when you turn 40 it's old when you
turn 45 it's old when you turn 50 it's old it you turn 55 I can we're going up a little higher
and and you don't realize it in the moment and so I only could tell you if you live through it
you're lucky but sometimes we sleepwalk through it anyway I'm getting too chatty but um no you're
I try to live like in the pause even though like I know like I'm kind of judgmental
but like I live try to live in the pause and
Meaning like you know, okay, like I'm gonna get okay
I'm gonna go there like you know like you'll get a tombstone like that when your birth and the death the dash is what's more important
The details right not the destination
the journey oh my god who the fuck am i talking so there's that
and i believe you're only as old as you feel i mean right you guys i mean it's just i don't
know there's these men like that i don't get it like
You don't understand. When I turned 50, I was like, Oh, my God, the like, you do the math, like, Oh, my God, half.
Like if you're lucky to make it to 100, oh, my, your half is over.
But then what if you slept walk through most of your fucking life?
So what's the difference?
Like you might just wake up on your last breath.
Then they say Steve Jobs, like at this last thing, go, Oh, oh, wait, what?
And then boom, you're out.
Like right when you figure out your fucking purpose, Steve Jobs is a retard.
Steve Jobs died.
Did you bring some cookies and a fresh loaf of bread?
I mean that guy right there, he's not a big looking guy with a full head of hair
He should like bow down and be happy be like thankful. Why does he got to come in like that sideways?
All right, and look we heard about the they the story of the Apple logo though like the original story. Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, okay. Go ahead. He was actually a gay man that when he went under
They gave him like testosterone shots and stuff to try to take a sexuality and his name is Alan
Alan something and he like invented like this coding like I'm gonna look it up real quick. Um, because this is a crazy story
It's like Apple logo story
And this guy's name is I want to know that story that sounds interesting
This is a story and so it's like it says uh, there's a so this is from CNN and this and the mythology says
that uh okay so it says if beauty is indeed truth as John Keats claimed then the story of
him ought to be true the logo in the back of your iphone or mac is attributed to Alan Turing the man
who laid the foundations for the modern-day computer pioneered research into artificial
intelligence and unlocked german wartime codes his death a decade after the end of the war provides
link with apple unrecognized first work facing jail for gross indecency and humiliated by estrogen
spirituality
He bit into an apple, he had laced with cyanide.
He died in obscurity on June 7th, 1954,
10 years and a day after the Normandy landings,
which made copious use of intelligence
and fleet by methods.
And so the story goes, when two Stanford entrepreneurs
were looking for a logo for the brand new computer company
they remembered touring and his contribution in their field.
They chose an apple, not a complete apple,
but one with a bite.
So I'm not laughing at you, I'm laughing with you.
Damn Apple story goes from the Bible to the Apple to the phone. I'm just joking. I'm being funny. Sorry carry on
But wait, but wait, but while you go into the historian part because we're all different the way our brains process stuff, right?
So when you're talking I'm very visual so my mind not that it didn't that that you're wrong. She's wrong
I'm wrong, but my perception is I'm I'm stuck on
When I said Steve Jobs, I'm stuck on here's a guy that thought he can control himself, right?
I'm thinking I wasn't there, but I'm just like thinking in my head and from what I read, like he wore like what?
The same black turtleneck may be like in the which would be easy, right?
You don't have to get close. You wear the same thing, right?
So and like, so there's persnicketing square, but yet very successful and never a quitter.
I'm thinking, OK, so with all that being said, he thought he had, I think he was Buddhist or something, something, something.
And then in the end from the storyline, which fascinates me.
Because I want to know, what did you see?
Like right when he's on the deathbed, so to speak,
and crossing, or before, like, wait, ah, ah.
Like if somebody like him would definitely
want to tell us, wait, wait, ah, there is Jesus.
Or wait, that's grandma.
Or wait, I was wrong.
Ah.
and then they yanked them out with like, you know, off the curtain or off the stage.
And so I'm so fascinated. All the money in the fucking world and everything that you have
in the end is just a human being like all this bone and blood and skin and in the end with the
soul, right? And in the end, no matter what you think you have control of, it could take you out.
That's my deep thoughts. Thank you. Have a nice day. All right, I'll be quiet. You give the mic now.
well yeah right it's a lot Alexandra's like oh my god did she just say all that who is this girl
i have a load of your mind but i'm nobody i'm really nobody but i mean i'm that yeah oh my god
no but well i i mean what you said about death really being the great equalizer that's kind of
Right and all the way and I'm sorry
I mean, you know when I get thoughts they rush in and they have to interrupt but interrupt me if I like your truth
Has to come out like quickly
But like you know how I believe in energy like when it's my time to talk and then you hand me the leaf or the feather or
Whatever and then your time to talk what what I want to say to you is and okay
Like I got so much to say like now that I'm talking but like I believe this too
Like our energy in other words if you're not your ego slash like in your head
cerebral as you would say, right? And there's a heart that's a million miles from the head,
the brain, the cerebral down to the heart, right? I mean, we've spent our whole life
trying to travel. And it's so close, right? But we're in our meat suits. But like, my point is,
like there is no time in space.
Okay, I know what I was gonna say.
So when you're in, okay, I'll just say this.
Oh my God, I'm losing her, John.
Wait, if, okay, you know the comment,
you know, like there's bumper stickers,
like, oh, it's cool to say, oh, yoga and blah, blah, blah.
Namaste, and you know, all that, and it's cool to say it.
But then I look deeper, what does that really mean?
I'm not gonna just say it
because I wanna be hip.
cool or fit in. I want to know what it means on a spiritual level. So then it means like
your God self makes your God self or my soul meets you and we're even with no ego, right?
So I read years ago.
right um when there came out more new agey stuff celestine prophecy there was a book
and then that became a movie and there was like 10 insights and i'm the type of person i don't
have to read like cover to cover like i'll just skim through and if i can pick out one thing in a
movie in a book like a one paragraph a chapter something that sticks with me and i tell this to
psyche all the time in my other slash kind of pretend friends like online screen names right
you know, when you're with somebody.
And you meet them halfway and there's no ego meaning a power struggle
That's a true beautiful slash soul friend or something where you're talking and when you stop talking like right now
I'm rambling but and then all of a sudden you pick up and your energy isn't like trying to conflict with me or
Power up or level up or ego
It's kind of like it's cool
And you're I'm feeding you a little bit and then you can be different than me discern right over there slash rabbis
like Jewish, but I'm open-minded.
So you go over there, like on the other hand,
then you add in and then we both go back and forth.
And the beauty of that is that we feed each other,
but we stay like on the seesaw in the playground.
We're like, you know, when we're kids seesaw,
you know, the thing and one goes up and you push your legs
and right, so the goal is that we stay equal
so we can converse without the battle,
but yet we feed each other because what else is the point?
as you get older, ageism. Hello, Joe. Just kidding. But as you get there and you go there,
you kind of say, if I get to the point where it's a battle and you're not going to have any gray
area or a little bit like, wait a minute, I'm not sure tomorrow. Let me discern. Let me think
about it. I think I'm right. But wait, let me resonate. Let me marinate, blah, blah, blah.
Then if you come back, you can say
Okay, I was wrong. I'm not all those sure that I was right and some people in your life
Are judgmental hardcore and they call themselves Christian?
Sorry, don't get mad and all these kind of things but on the other
Yes, and on the other hand, we don't all the way know we know as best we know
But then but then we have to meet where they're at the energy, but yet keep it keep it
keep it where I mean I recognize that there's some people when you get to a point in your life
be it you could call yourself getting older or it could be young at 30 it doesn't matter
that if you get like you know it's too much of a struggle to have you in my life anymore I can't
battle it I can't change your mind and if you're making it more you're taking from a nut adding to
I'm like I'm loving I'm forgiving but I'm not going to be a schmuck I can't be forgiving where I
purpose and my own sole purpose. So I love you. I forgive you, but you need to go because
it's taking out of me. Feel me, sister. Okay.
I so know where you're coming from because, um, this year specifically, I've gone through
a bit of a cleansing process when it comes to people in my life, people who I love, people
who I respect, but people who I just can't deal with because I'm not willing to fight.
Yeah, I will not appease you but I understand you and I will walk away from you. Yeah, and if necessary I will
pretend like you don't exist anymore. Yeah, I hate you. So no, no, no, but I recognize I've
watched, you know, I kind of watched a little bit about you and chew, you chew, you know, laugh,
because I mean, well, but you know, I can be judgmental too. But I will say, because you're
on the internet slash putting it out there, you're big AKA, I'm a big slash when you say AKA, AKA,
I'm laughing with you, not at you, my friend, but no, no, the hugs, hugs, major hugs right
now because I'm open because
She knows no, I'm glad you're talking so much. I've been talking all day and I know right
Yeah, I looked at some of your old streams. I did a little like like a little deep dive on you
I'm like, I love three years ago whenever was and you did those cooking streams. You meant well
I you know, even if it wasn't perfect, you almost cut your finger off and one but it was so beautiful a foodie
But no, I
So don't get a twisted sister. I saw you wait. What did she do?
Right. Oh my God. I saw it.
No stiller laugh.
No, but I saw it, but I thought it was so cool because you're in your joy.
You didn't give a two shits.
Who's watching or not? Right there.
Chop, chop, chop.
But like, I thought that was cool and I hope you find whatever it is.
And I know you put it out there and I know you're strong and you're tough and,
and, and.
and and and hopefully you're pivoting around um because we can't control what other viewers lurkers eyeballs right now i'm scared to death because there's people right now going who the fuck is joni so i want to disappear off this panel because i'm nobody i'm not a live streamer i don't mean
anybody anything and there's many people in these as you say communities that don't like or they're they're going to go you just set up a mush mouth of nothing and why do i care i said what i actually said a lot
Right. Right. Right. Right. So sometimes like you said something recently, sometimes like hate and
love is real close. And sometimes at the projection parts, what somebody triggers you are like,
you feel a certain way, then you have to step in. Okay, what the fuck? Like, is it something that is
about me that I'm seeing in them? But I know like years of sitting in a console or a therapist's
office, that just gets chatter in my head. Then I end up wanting to be friends with them anyway,
So it's like a weird thing. It's only humbling to realize that why all we can do is figure out ourself
if there's a common thing that happens over and over we have to pivot the mirror like Michael Jackson
remembering that song the man in the mirror like somehow eventually and it sucks because I would
rather point outwards not inwards it's so much easier to dumb out numb out so but there's all
of that and you want so there it goes all right now now that's it well I heard like here earlier
There were how there's some more viewership to the negative hate hateful
Streams and the positive yes streams, but our brains are wired to be attracted to conflict. Yes
That's what the algorithms even are based on
But you can't pay attention to that because you have to think to yourself, okay
What do I want to feed my soul with?
Yes, or negativity. Yes, and that's something I really consciously think about nowadays right guys for many years
I fed my spirit with a lot of negativity and it took a toll on me and now I'm doing the opposite
consciously and it's hard to do the positive because we're surrounded by the negative and
sometimes people don't understand or align with you vibrationally when you shift that.
wait Alexander I don't even want to call the name is so long I almost want to call you a I just want
to say call me a I have a sense of humor that's really weird when I get nervous so I'm like real
slapstick and right away I saw the scene of harry met Sally and when I kept saying yes yes yes
No, but I think the other thing too, it's really weird when people talk when I say ageism and that's just a word
And you're really good with your words and you're really like smart and you are the only you know
No, no, no, you may not be you may not be all the way because there's I see blind spots
But however your your tone your inflection. What do you call cadence?
Cadence or whatever that word is you are very that is elegant
You do have the and I said people get mad at me, but I'm not saying Oprah or you said Candace Owens
all of that you are masterful Oprah is my idol girl I know and you have all that and you and I'm
like get out of this fuck where you're at and level up because you could do it I mean you you
have you're just having so anyway that's just I those are just private thoughts every now and then
but um well thank you you're welcome and I recognize it and sometimes like I say to like
you know well will you sit into your weight to my left and you're right maybe in a square
But I say why should we start with right right right? It could be the Brady Bunch
It could be Hollywood skirs, whatever, but but you know
But back to the age of some and then I'm gonna get off because I think I've said too much
Yes, you in the corner. That's me in the wait. Sorry
but
As we get older isn't it weird listen listen listen me says isn't it weird in a weird way when we're born like out of the womb
Slash out of the body. Okay slash see your a.k.a. I'm a slash girl
We forget like somehow God Jesus hire self
takes away our any memory of why we're here or if we're sent here or if we're like a it's a contract. I
don't know we come out and we forget everything like don't you know like you just like you you just
hear and then in the end it glimpses of it though glimpses you're right you're right you're right
little little glimpses okay if you're aware otherwise okay depends depends if you had knee socks or
I don't want to age myself. Hello. Just kidding. Um, Nick Kerr is not, you know, the hard art. Sorry. Just kidding. No offense. But anyway, I know what you're doing. I have an issue. I have an issue, but I, but I'm trying to like, it's okay. Getting to know you. Right? Okay. Listen, listen, listen. I think at the weird part as we age up, no matter what your age is.
It's all like, for some reason, I go and I go, I'll show us Joey, but I have a cat that's meowing.
I kind of want to go, why is it...
We spend this part of our life, the first 20 years, but then as we go up, it's all in the unlearning, the unpeeling, the reverse.
So as we get aged up, our body's kind of like dying or getting older, it's only and then you're like becoming, and then you're kind of like, wait, and then you try to go back to the sweet spot of the innocence before the sin or the tormented thoughts or like what your parents said or whatever, and you take it in depending on how you're, you're like your stride of life is like, am I going to be like.
Oh, quiet or the rebel or invisible
as you're growing up as a kid, right?
Like almost involuntary.
I said a lot to you, girl.
I just want you to know kind of who I am.
Like I'll mic drop it at that.
Should I leave?
Should I moonwalk backwards, John?
Well, I mean, Psyche.
Whatever you feel like.
Why are you making that face and pressing your error?
Am I bothering you?
He's almost like my dad is.
I mean, I could be long stalking.
We'll see.
Who needs what he extends is when I keep pulling.
it. Hopefully it doesn't pull out. And by the way, I'll leave you here. Well, well, anyway,
it was nice to see you. And I'm sorry that, wait, uh, yes, yes.
I'm glad you got to let me let my guard I like talking to you.
I I've been judgmental.
I've been looking at you.
I don't know.
I guess I'm kind of powerful, but not.
I've been looking at you, sister, but I'm not like sometimes in a good way.
But tonight when you came up, I had a choice.
I could get into my ego and my judgment or I can just relax and take it in the present
moment that yesterday you're like, like what I say you're all your stuff you put on like
Okay, wait, you changed your mind,
and you reversed, and you U-turn,
and then you're talking about this one,
and that one, I'm like, what is she doing?
She's so talented, or she could be doing something else.
Why does she keep going?
Just go back and put that fucking lamb
that you like on the counter, and chop it up sis.
But anyway, I digress.
And it's only because I wanna find more what's in common.
and and not fight it and so tonight I let it in I just want you to know it took a minute and while
you there because I'm looking at your face because you're on my big screen oh my god my cat's running
around um yeah I have a big screen too big so I'm looking I'm looking at you relaxed and I'm like
not fighting it like this that's how everyone can hear this who doesn't get it turn it off judge me
hate me the ones that get it if it's just a couple then I did what you call God's work or my purpose
of you another person. We can read the storylines, we can judge them, we can listen, the inflections.
And yet, if we just for a second put our arms down and maybe go, wait a minute,
and then you see the good in something, what are they having good? What do we have in common
versus what we don't have? And if you let it in, maybe we laugh together. Maybe there's something
like the brick and mortar and the paperback book,
I'm more in because of the way I grew up
in more of the viable, the action of it.
And then I have to meet it halfway upwards towards the heavens.
Did I say a lot?
I hope you got something from it.
I'm gonna hang, I'm leaving now, I'm so embarrassed.
All right, I love you guys.
That's it.
I let her in, Johnny boy, I let her in.
Bye.
Thank you.
Have a good night.
She's sweet. Yeah, she is very sweet and very interesting her mind works fast
And yeah, mine works fast too and yours does too.
I think we're very intelligent people.
I wish you had stayed longer
because I would have liked to have told her
that a lot of people ask me sometimes,
like, why are you talking to that person?
What are you doing here?
You should be doing more, but it's all a process.
You know, I think back when I was younger,
about
Things that people question me about doing, but if I hadn't done those things. I definitely
wouldn't
Have a certain level of happiness that I have right now
So I think everything's for a reason right and you wouldn't be who you are either like without all of your
Every single decision you made to this point right right now. You're the person you are and that is beautiful. Yeah
Like and you are a beautiful person and it's like, I mean really
And so are you Joanie if you're still out there, I think you are I can kind of tell
Right and that's why I'm like no matter what people are saying they're like, oh well, you know
He has no people that support him. I say I have the best people that support me
I have the best people that love me. I like I have the best people
This whole thing going on right now
I'm really glad it's going on right now.
I think that this has been a conversation
within these communities.
And you're in those communities.
Don't let anybody tell you, oh, we're not gonna talk.
You're in there, that's why they're talking about you.
But there have been some lies.
that have been told there have been some power plays within these groups of people a
very high level of manipulation and
I
Think some people are being blackmailed to an extent, but they can't say anything about it. I kind of get that
feeling yeah
I've like if I'm wrong about something I will say I'm wrong or if I'm unsure
I'll just you know put it on the table until I am sure and
That's gonna know what I did today, and I feel good about I think I made the right choice when it came to you
Removing some things from online
I'm glad I took the time early this morning to or I guess called last night slash this morning to watch that dude
He was saying some interesting things to anything that he had to say and it's been several months
Yeah, and that's why I don't believe in the really silencing anybody because so many people
I mean like oh, they don't deserve a place to talk
They don't deserve a voice and it's like well, how will they defend themselves?
How do they so I deserve everyone having a chance to even it's on their own platform or something like that to say what they
really feel and not and not uh, you know
Be afraid because it's like and they really right now. It's like people
Threatening people and say yeah
Right, I mean it is I mean it's like it is and it's like the fact that the fact that you are willing to listen
ruling to listen to him and and hear what he had to say and
You know imagine if he didn't have the chance to say what he said and it's like maybe sometimes
that that one guy
CA's buddy, Ganval, he was, he backpedaled today. And he did, he did make it known that
he, he lied about that dude, you know, he was make, he was saying very clearly before
That oh, well, he's technically this and that but here on the internet. We just say this
Yeah, this isn't here on the internet
Real life
We can't say anything with that, you know
someone's someone's 17 days or 17 years and 364 days to the 18th birthday and you're like oh that's
that's wrong and then the day later it'll be okay you know it's like really it's they just want
certain people just want to pick and choose who's in and who's out and i mean if you want to do that
cool you know that's what the uh tabloids always do but just admit that you're a tabloid if that's
We're not the National Enquirer here. I'm not the National Enquirer. I'm not like, you know, trying to be sensational and just get attention for sensationalists.
I really want the truth. That's what I'm about. And so if I'm telling the truth and if people don't like it, then it's like, you know, they're not meant to be on my life.
You know, RG, porn bomb me. Q, porn bomb me. J doggie.
RG did?
Yes, RG did.
He never turns his camera on.
I mean, no, he tried. He would do the backstage. I saw his name. His name was RG backstage. And we were showing you better.
Okay, I have a quick thought. I was I just had to pee like I'm in a one-bedroom
So like if I pee I can hear you okay TMI so I want before I wanted to say this to you
Thank you for being so kind and saying that I heard what you said you you you you a but but what I want to say to you is
Okay, listen listen. This is so important
Even the reason I flew up today,
flew up onto this panel because Joe,
and I know he's got lots of good points.
This is a guy on the internet and there's bad and good and all.
I get it and it's a game and fun and blah, blah, blah.
I want him or you or anyone here to know that.
Even if I came up kind of sounding angry or
or competitive in the end, thank you.
Thank you in a weird way because it was you that
brought me up that gave me the gift of meeting you.
And that opened my heart to talk to you.
So if people could expand themselves and realize even if
something looks like.
oh what the heck are they doing here or they're icky or whatever you realize once you live through
it and survive through it you're stronger better bigger and you can do more and I just want to
recognize that does that make sense it does make sense you actually made me think about something
in regards to what I was just talking about with psyche when it came to this guide known as seah
His situation and my thoughts on it. It was a little bit hard for me because I am actually scared of that particular guy
Yes, but I think to myself maybe if other people had listened to him more
Yeah, and where he was coming from he wouldn't have become so scary to where there you go
I don't like being scared of anybody. No at all
and I don't like that
somebody who is willing to look at him would feel as I do,
and I feel like there's a lot around him that's conducive to him basically being isolated.
Oh, go ahead.
Okay. I'm jumping like the game of like,
I'm very visual, so I have my eyes closed.
I'm like the game of, you know, like growing up like jump rope, right?
Can I get in? Can I get in?
So you tried your way I'm forgive me if I overstep here and you tried your way meaning like you know
Reporting so to speak factual or what you thought or like you're standing up for the underdog or no
You're gonna expose all of the above but on the other hand as they say in retrospect
The empathy slash compassion as you grow as a soul person
I would think you kind of go wait a minute. Maybe I think I'm a hundred percent, right?
But you know what, I'm still just human.
Wait, let me look a little more.
And it took, to me in my opinion, it took a long time.
Like once you say the word and it leaves your lips and voice,
we can't put the shit back in the toothpaste tube, right?
So that's the problem for all of us.
Like once you say it, it's mighty.
And you put it out there, it's heard and seen.
And you don't know who and how they're gonna receive it.
Now on you as a human, like searching along
then go wait and then switch it around or you to it around and say, wait a minute, maybe
I wasn't all the way right. And you admit it, which is a beautiful thing in my opinion.
Not that you have to, but then it shows a humbleness and a vulnerability.
It feels better. It feels better to admit when you are wrong about stuff. I don't care
what anyone has to say about me. Like if I could like speak to you like is like a hello.
Like, but, but, but, but you went hard the other way and I'm not saying it, but it's
too late.
You can't go back and get it off the street, so to speak.
It's already out there, but you can, like he said, I held you like in judgment if you
must know, like, why did she keep an over and over and I get it.
But then, and then I was like, wait, I'm not going to like when she's talking now and she's
you turning, wait a minute.
Who am I to hang you up on the damn cross? Get off the cross. We need the wood.
So let this lady breathe, thrive. Like not that I'm anybody, but I open myself just tonight
because Josh, what is his name? Shippley, Shippley, whatever. Sorry, Joe. Just no, thank you. Again,
thank you for being such a dick. Just kidding. But anyway, I'm not even looking at the screen,
because I don't know if you're laughing or you hate me, but um.
But, you know, I know you don't know.
I think you're funny.
I know funny as well.
Get out.
No, I'm not.
I'm the self deprecating human.
You're also a good assessor because I know a bit of what
you're talking about, but you don't necessarily say it.
You're just no right.
You dance around things around where you are.
Yeah, right.
And at least you can get it because I
do think you could get it.
I thought you're so like to that way of it.
because you're more like the way you're,
what I would say, terminology, you're very elegant,
you know how to flow it, and that, and that's beautiful.
And what I can bring to the table,
like if we only could like make like a,
I'm not a computer, but if we were a robot or something,
if I could put part of me in there and part of you,
maybe a little psyche and a couple other whatever,
tablets and I'm just saying, I'm joking.
But I have something to add too.
So I look at you and just cause you might have,
oh, accolades and you lived life, man.
You took the chances, even if for whatever,
you did it, I didn't.
I kind of went up to the edge and looked and I'm like,
and I ran back so I didn't try it and I didn't do it all the way but you did and I was salute that
you still can I know well maybe I don't know but maybe yes maybe but you know it's like I mean
so yeah but but really all I really wanted to say is even in
I'm not just talking about tonight's experience everything that happens to us if we breathe through it and live through it to the next day
Or a couple hours that can be devastating punch-gutting, right?
You have somebody that just like pulled the
Will like like you know how you look at like a trap door like you're walking and all of a sudden
Well, the whole bottom came out a good friend a family member
Somebody like you trusted boom and you didn't see it coming like what the
right? But if you can breathe through it and look through it, no matter what their lessons are,
all you can do is the best you can with yours and discern. Soak in it a little bit like your
little sauteed, little stove, and your little cooking. It's all connected. We can bring that in
now from three or four years ago. I'm giving permission. I'm waving in those dishes. I saw you
What do you want me to cook the next time?
I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna.
Amiga lamb, amiga lamb, I'd love to see a lamb.
I may have lamb just the other day.
Oh, not with the lamb already.
That's probably why I feel so heavy.
Wait, so much, wait, so much lamb.
Okay, but you know what I like?
One of my favorite things.
I love lamb.
Of course, a nice glass, I know, I get it, but you know,
I like, you know, with a nice, depending on the wine, like a nice red, there's nothing
more romantic.
Peanut noir.
Peanut noir, I'm kind of a cabbie, but like if you're in the kitchen and I don't even
care if you have, you know, slippers on a tank top, it doesn't matter.
You have a little chill music in the background, the lights are dimmed down.
So the ambiance and you're cooking, the smells, the beauty, it's, and then if you find a,
I love being in the kitchen, all of it, all of it, all of it, all of it.
The cooking on the on this community you were the first one to do the cooking. But wait, I want wait wait
I'm calling her a a my a friend. I want to say to you what I like
Um
Is I know that maybe and you could probably do a chicken or maybe lamb even our steak
I like searing so if you get your pot and it could even be an iron like you know season pot
and you get that and a little maybe olive oil drizzle and you put the steak or the filet mignon
or whatever your choice of the meat is right and you sear it
and you get it real like where it's like on the outside flip it and the inside isn't all
way done and then put that like maybe on warm a little in the oven and now what the beauty part
is is that's kind of slow in the oven now we're going to come back up top now what do we want to
do do we want to slice up some like with the bits you know the bits the fat so now we're going to
like we have to be careful I don't know I'm talking like this but I was going on units
But anyway, so then you take it so then you have to be careful because you know olive oil or butter one of the two alone burn
So you have to cut it with the other right? So you have the bits of that that's hearing steak. Let's say steak
Let's do steak tonight. So we steak both sides are kind of like and it's depending on the if you if you're like somebody really kind
Of crazy girl you would have that kind of
that skillet that has like the grill marks if you wanted to go there right like a barbecue but it's
not a barbecue like blah blah blah. My mom has one of those. Right right right okay and there's
like a theory to that iron cast to have it seasoned I'm thinking it's dirty get it like SOS pad no but
it means something so you have to be from those times plus it's heavy I could just lift those
forget about the weights but anyway um yeah cast and plus the calamity comes in and they're not
supposed to be there get out of my way hit them on the head just kidding. Yeah you can beat somebody
Yeah, that's right.
Right, real quick.
It's a weapon.
It will feed you, but it will protect you.
It will feed you and protect you.
Yes, yes, yes.
Who knew we were doing an infracomersal for the new pan?
Just anyway.
Yeah, well, this new pan, they're not like the old.
I like the old fashion ones better.
No, no, right.
Okay.
But listen, wait, I can't finish because I can't think.
Wait, wait, wait.
back to the sauteing. So once you take the steak off, whatever you have those bits, right?
So now we're going to add a little bit of butter, maybe a little more olive oil.
And now we're going to say, do we want to saute some mushrooms? Do we want to put a
little garlic? Do we want a little onion? And we don't want to brown it. We don't want to burn it.
Be careful now. And we like those mushrooms that are all different shapes. And I don't mean an
it was very much like that. I don't know. I'm doing it the most of them are clean. It
doesn't matter, but I like all the of
variety of mushrooms. But anyway, right, throw that in. Okay, Mrs. Bobby, come on in. Right.
Can you imagine being so mad at someone just like they're sleeping and they're like passed
out and you take a night, cut it off and run down the street and throw it out the window.
Right. And then go back and get it stoned on. You're so lucky. But anyway,
I just remember what you wanted to cast straight Sam and that was that was it a big stream.
Yeah, she was like, see, man, I would just chop it off.
Yeah, let me finish my, my, my, my, my recipe.
I'm gonna get all cooking.
I mean, right now there's a skillet in my mind's eye.
Like it's, I'm not on acid, I swear.
I'm not tripping.
This is just my brain cells.
So, so I'm, get passionate and I get excited.
So with that, with our, with our pan on the top
are little stuffs in the oven.
Now they also call it tinting.
If you took the silver foil and even if you turn the oven off
and you put the tent like foil over it,
It kind of warms it and keeps cooking, but on a low.
It's like, you know what I'm saying?
Or like maybe you brought it up.
But what I like about the-
Oh, tinting.
I thought you said tinny.
Okay, okay.
Tinny, no, tin-t-t-t-t-i-n-t.
Yes, I don't know.
But anyway, so after we get our musters,
if we decide mushrooms or whatever we want,
now we got this going on.
Or like, oh, now what?
Guess what?
You bring in your Pino, I bring in my Cabin,
and even could be a cheap,
because it's not really for the purpose of us drinking.
We're gonna pour it in, we're gonna have it on high range
where it's like, but then we gotta be careful
because it can get too watery.
So then we have to keep watching,
add maybe a little more butter, stirring, stirring.
Like, you know how you like to saute, stirring, stirring
and now it becomes syrupy.
Feel me, sister?
therapy, but you have to be careful.
Now, I would like to take the thing out of the oven now,
drizzle the tap, and you know what,
I'm gonna throw something on, you may not like it,
but I even like a little bit of a blue cheese crumble,
because I kind of like-
Well, I do like blue cheese.
I love it.
I've never had it.
I never had it like that though.
It's beautiful like it on the steak, I'm just saying.
It's good.
I mean, I know, right?
Not only that, but if you did like not only asparagus,
I love asparagus
Right, asparagus, except for the year, I mean, let's come later, you forget you had a couple drinks and you had like the middle of the night, like what the hell?
I'm smelling asparagus in my pee. I don't know. Sorry, there's a little black out there.
She goes like this, and then there's that, but who cares? I'm single, I don't give a shit.
Did you put the lid down on the toilet or raise it up? It's an issue.
Laughing from the inside. Oh, I know I'm gonna pay. I'll be on the headlines of the internet next tomorrow trolled like no get out
Okay, so um anyway back to our steak. So but here's the thing
We don't have the steak back up there yet. Now. I like when you talk about crumbled blue cheese
Now Brussels sprouts growing up. You know how like when you're kid
Oh, you don't like vegetables or your belly to get your parents be it broccoli be at this be at that
And I never like brussels, but they're stinky.
However, if you roast them a little bit, right?
And then you put the crumble on with a little drizzle
of olive oil, I mean, how good is that?
Because there's so much beautifulness in it.
Well, I like all vegetables.
I don't think there's any vegetable I don't like.
Right.
Mm.
right. My sister makes the best like I think my favorite dish on Thanksgiving is her Brussels sprouts
and they're just like you know Thanksgiving there's twice as much as everything. They're like burnt
like a burnt like a burnt but not burnt you know what I mean. Oh they're just really they're really
good you know. Yes. I want a poetry contest about lima beans. I don't think I still like lima beans
but I didn't want to poetry contest when I was in second grade. I was actually. I don't like lima
Beans, right?
Yeah, but I don't like lima beans.
Well, you could learn, you may be,
sometimes it's mental, but something like mental,
meaning like you have an upset,
but like, like you can maybe come towards it.
The lima bean, not a day Navy bean,
but the lima bean, it's a pain in how you season it.
Now I know this is weird, but I have this thing for,
basil. I don't know what's up with that. It smells good. It smells good. And there's something too.
Okay, so then because I still have my beautician licensee when I'm not actively using it,
but I remember long ago a class. I remember a VEDA, I don't know if they have it anymore,
a VEDA was like a certain line. A VEDA. A VEDA. A VEDA. Is it like shampoo?
they talk about um the memory of like safe skin lotion you have or like well you know like
you have like you smell gasoline or fresh cracked grass or fire your fireplace it takes you right
back to childhood isn't that amazing and weird how that can do that like we don't pay a lot of
I think scent is like the most underrated underrated and if you okay if you
I'll say something and then I'm gonna dip out again
you, young lady. Oh my God, I'm in so much trouble tonight. A, my friend A, if you, instead
of just talking, just don't get mad about the Bible, if you talk like this and I got
to know you, then I might say, but what are you, okay, what are you reading over there?
Instead of first coming that way, this way, I'm like, wow, she's real. I can meet her
And then maybe we'll talk about that versus if you go the reverse way and you do it, I get scared like, oh,
Holier than that wait fair judgment. I'm a lot of people think I think I'm yeah
Because yeah, I'm doing yeah, I'm reading because I always wanted to know you always wanted to but in the bible and right
I'm going from pay. I'm going straight through in order right whenever I have a chance
My grandfather was um
you know, he was like always very skeptical his whole life, but then when he was in the 70s or 80s,
he read the Bible from beginning to end. I wanted to understand the Bible.
But like, and I'm doing it verbally because I feel like there might be people in my family who,
you know, you know, the visual I got, you know what I got when you're talking, the visual I got is
like, I know this is like child, like a child's book, like, you know, the books you open up and they
Right. So if you're talking, if it could just pop up, if the Bible pieces could pop up and where I can visually like go back because I wasn't there or was I right, like in a past life.
So I'm kind of like I'm taking the viewpoint of perceptions of people that were there and then I listen to the story and I can't relate it to my real time.
But but yet if I could be like talking to you and we're walking around and we're living life.
story versus talk about the story first and then bring me, that's the switch up.
That's the switch up that I'm having a hard time and I'm hoping that you're flexible enough
to hear me and allow maybe a discernment in there just a little bit because, yeah, all
of the above.
Oh my God, I second that.
Well, my Bible reading, it's actually kind of a selfish thing I'm doing and I'll tell
you.
Yeah, okay.
do the reading. You know, since I've been reading the Bible, I have had so many themes from it,
basically, like you just said, pop up occur in my day to day life to where I do catch myself
sometimes just having conversations with people, like if I'm at the grocery store or whatever.
and don't tell me something, and then it does take me in my mind to maybe a recent book of the Bible that I read.
So, wait, I gotta jump in.
So for me, I'm just kind of doing it to expand my own knowledge base because when I read things out loud, I remember them better than when I, you know, just read to myself.
I didn't know that. As a person out here, FYI,
judgmental like girl like way over here like why and I look at that but now hearing you in real
time describe the why's and so forth it makes I'm a little a lot more like oh because otherwise my
wall was up like we what and it's like a resistance now I want to say to you too um
I like that when you read it maybe for selfish reasons or that you always wanted to but you happen to be putting on a format out into the public right which is
It's on my personal channel. I know I know I know I know I know but but
What I like about what you just said is what you're reading it and going through it right page to page
But I like later and you go to the grocery store and you're out like walking around all of a sudden like the pop-up book something comes up and then you're like
oh that's what they meant because the brain works in a way I'm thinking you're reading it
educationally you're taking it and trying to learn it but it's hard to flip it into the real life
our human life and we're flawed right and we sometimes get like in fear and judgment and
but it's so cool that if you can say wait
oh that's why that is and then you put it together and it resonates versus just reading it. Sometimes I
do like a personal thought before I get into whatever chapter of whatever book of the Bible
it is that I'm in. Right now I'm in like the most boring of the books which is Chronicles because
For me, the whole thing is an exercise.
It's an exercise in my pronunciation of things.
It's an exercise when it comes to me
knowing the concrete details of what's in the Bible.
It's an exercise in my spirituality,
because I do believe that there is a level of power
within any sort of religious texts that you read.
And I do see a lot of the manifestations of that
in my life.
It's a very interesting thing.
So you know what I, let's go ahead.
Most importantly, because it's audio, I really want some of my family members who are younger than me to, you know, who might be a little bit resistant to anything spiritual.
You know, forget about Christianity as, you know, Christianity. That's my choice.
But I just want my younger family members to kind of use spirituality as a cool thing because a lot of the young kids, they don't believe in anything.
Right. Right.
what I do take issue with and it lives on and um I want to say um yeah and I want to say to you
now I forgot my thought wait wait wait I'm sorry no don't worry I was trying to jump in but you
wouldn't stop for that said to me I wouldn't let you
No, you wouldn't let me, which meant you needed to go on,
which is what we were talking about before.
If you let me, then like spirit like in my mind was like,
okay, wait, let me turn the baton over to her
because she's got something to add.
And then you go back and we go back and forth, right?
Like a friendly sword match, so to speak.
But, yeah, no, it's so good.
It's all good.
I'm really pleased to see that within you.
I think you're just you're just thriving. Don't worry about that you're
the 47, 48, don't give a fuck.
You're just thriving, you're just beginning.
And everything, like you say, like he said,
it brings you to here, but there is some regrets
or maybe some choices, but it doesn't matter.
And don't worry and don't quit saying like,
oh, I'm getting so old.
No, to me, you're so young and so beautiful.
And you just need to like flower
and whatever that is to be.
And I'm not gonna say anymore
because we're on live stream
and the world is kind of mean a lot of these people.
So I'm not gonna say it.
out loud and I don't need to.
But I feel very much forgiveness is a big fucking thing
and you can't make someone do it.
And sometimes it is too late
and sometimes people don't forgive you back.
So you do it for you or sometimes you forgive
but you can't forget.
There's just so many chapters and layers to it.
And we keep as long as we keep.
I don't know. They're so deep. I just so much enjoy. Thank you for letting me speak. Thank you for letting me hear
Thank you for letting me let thank you. Joni for like for being open and forgiving and adjuvant judgment
Thank you Joe for being such an asshole and saying that I'm some fucking old whore. I appreciate you
Thank you for that. You you hillbilly. He ain't young you old fuck you ugly. No, just kidding
You raised his best. No, I didn't say anything. No, no, but thank you
things yeah you know good rotten no but he knows thank you thank you Joe thank
you yeah right all right I gotta go I gotta go I gotta go like I don't know
feed a bird pet a cat do something maybe pee again anyway PMI all of the above
All the above and then some, all at once.
And always remember, just like what is the Bob Barker
where you say about the animals.
I get a stay in your head.
Always wipe from front to back is all I gotta say.
Oh my God.
Well.
I mean, right, right, right, right, right.
I'm out.
Thank you, Jeremy.
Good night, good night.
I'm not sleeping anywhere.
Trust me, I'll be up all night.
But it's night to you.
for real. All right. And now I'm gonna see you soon. For real. Namaste. So the sources. Bye. Love
you. Bye. Love you. Bye. Bye. Yeah. Great conversation. A great conversation is also great
to like, you know, people we don't think we can get along with sometimes or we have judgments
about if we talk to them, it's a completely different thing and I love that she brought
up a few things because you know, I didn't
I knew when I started the Bible reading on my Alexandra channel. It was probably going to be perceived a certain way
I didn't know that but
That's just what my channel over there is right now, you know, it just kind of is but I'm happy about it because
That's a big part of who I am right now
Yeah, and I'm sorry if I ever put any judgment on that that wasn't serious. It's like I don't think any well
It's a lot of times people are afraid to say anything to me. I have come to that realization
So it's nice to you know get real solid authentic feedback about what people think and you know, maybe I need to do an explanation
Stream one day about why you know what I was just telling your friend because that's what it is
There's a lot of reasons. I'm doing that page by page reading at the Bible. It's not
So much to convince anyone to be Christian. It's more so
just so I can know exactly what is in the Bible.
It's sort of almost like a ritual for me to,
you know, I try to do it every day.
I don't get to do it every single day,
but it just, it has done something for me that I've needed.
So after the Bible,
I guess I'll have to read something else.
I don't want to check out those and I want to check out your your live
Well wait until I'm out of the book of chronicles because chronicles I am struggling through that because it's just
basically a genealogical list of names and it's just it's almost become almost like
a dear diary before I get into that the actual reading of
you know, whatever the chapter is, because some of those names, it's a little bit of a humbling
experience trying to pronounce some of those names, but I do like that that book exists,
because it's kind of like a review of everything I've read so far.
So I'm excited about the New Testament.
Let me see how many more chapters I have
before you get there.
Yeah, I mean, I didn't read what is considered the Torah,
like which is like the first five books of the Bible.
I think it was Genesis, Leviticus, Exodus,
Deuteronomy and Numbers and those are the first five books
which is the first.
And I read the Kabbalah explanation of them
where they get into Lilith and things like that.
and uh we have we have you do join me wait i i i have one more thing there's never one more thing
right right my friend a i i had i want to say something to you i i i'm very visual and i do
my head always goes to movies okay so so even though i'm older than you like i like my move it
doesn't matter
Just feel me on this, sis.
Feel me on this.
I'm thinking of the last scene in Oprah Winfrey,
the color purple.
And do you remember the scene with Sugar?
She was saying-
And I have purple.
I have a purple light on right now.
And I would, purple light, yes.
Purple, right?
No, we won't talk about him, but whoa, my God,
what a talent.
Well, I like Prince.
But Prince, hello, hello, hello, dolly.
But listen, the last scene,
and what you talked about your dad,
not to be personal, but the little bit I know,
and I get it, kind of, but not.
but I'm pretty intuitive.
What I want to say to you is the last scene
when she was like, quote, a sinner, what her dad was,
very Baptist, maybe Southern, like blah, blah, blah,
blah, the black church, right?
And the old days, and she was just singing
and walking down the, if you remember the last scene,
you know, it was Shug, that one.
And she's singing and she's got a beautiful voice
and her dad's all judgmental and cut him out of the life.
I'm thinking about you for some reason with this.
And then the dad, when she comes in and like daddy
and he opened up, he has like in that old black,
or the robe or whatever, and he opened up his big arms
and brought her in, and it was so beautiful.
And I don't know why, but I mentioned it to Psyche
the other day about that movie when you were talking,
not talking to you yet, and I just want you to know
in a weird way, when I think about your dad or whatever,
that like the old school and that religion, la, la, la,
and then yet in the end, he wanted to love his daughter
and she only wanted love from him,
but there was like judgment and fear,
but in the end, she got to do it.
while they were still above the grass, as they say. All right, that's all I got. I got to go
because otherwise... No, I'm glad you said that. Yeah, I hope that landed. Did that land? Should I
say a little bit more? Do you got it? Did you get it? No, no, I think I... Go ahead, go go.
Well, I think about my dad a lot. I know, I know. I started that Bible reading
around the time that I learned that he was sick.
And, um, it helped me get through, yeah, some of the tougher times before he crossed over.
Mm hmm.
Yes.
Yeah.
And it's just.
It's amazing.
Right.
Yeah.
It's something that I will do to completion because.
Yes.
He's with me yes in those moments because I was you know
I told him that I'd started the project and I remember I was on the phone with his sister
Well, I was at his house while I was telling him that and his sister said
No one reads the Bible cover to cover and I was like well, I do and then my dad piped up
He was like
My daughter does a lot of things that people don't do.
Yes.
The apple of her eye.
No matter what the disagreements and whatever,
and the diversity and the difference and the color,
I don't mean color like that.
I mean, colorfulness of the soul's lifestyle.
You know what I'm saying?
So it's,
It's so good. And now he's such like a guardian angel and a guy to you in a weird way. Whatever we call the other time, I can feel my dad's presence around me. Yes. Yes. Yes. All right. I love you. Got to go. I got to go because I'm big. Oh, maybe you might come back.
You might come back in 10 minutes again, especially you're in the new revelations
that's when the most of Jews have to cut off. No, we don't believe that, but I'm like, wait,
why not? Like, wait, I want Christmas too. She's kind of funny. I'm like, don't leave. I like her.
She's actually kind of funny.
Oh, thank you very much.
And by the way, can I talk shit or where can I talk shit or NorCal?
I've been waiting very patiently to talk shit or NorCal.
We're going to have some shit. Go ahead, Joe.
OK.
Well, it's like most of us up here.
Most of us up here don't have families.
We're single.
We have nothing to do.
So we joined panel.
But North Cal's like a six year old guy with a family.
This faggot knows all the lures.
Like, OK, that's your family.
North Cal, you're fucking faggot.
He's a faggot too.
He's a faggot loser, man.
He is.
He's a faggot.
You're a loser.
I love going to steak. He's like, he's like, I can't stop going there.
Nobody has a family here, but NorCal. And the niggers still here.
Maybe your family, maybe me,
you should grow up and be your own family and interchangeable parents.
10 minutes ago, I thought you had to go to bed at 10 minutes ago.
No, I'm staying. He doesn't have to go to bed.
I ain't going anywhere, mother fucker.
Come on, no, I mean, it's like, it's like, you have a bunch of people in your chat right now.
So I'm pretty sure that you're my guy. Oh my God. I'm so scared. Oh my God.
I think you're enjoying the conversation. I think that's please enjoy.
I'm going to take care of your family. No, no, no, no, no. Here's what I don't want.
I don't know the norcal. I don't know the the the lore as they say and I just I'm up here for a different purpose
So even though I enjoy the freedom of speech you go and it's content
I kind of want to dip because I don't want to be associated with it and have that like kind of ick energy
Not that you do you and I'm not saying you're wrong. I got me
But don't let him chase you because he did interject saying what he said specifically to me
you on. Oh, he plays that game. That's why I want to take that word from. Oh, I'm taking
it from him. Soon he's not going to be able to have that effect.
Yeah, that's a little bit of a life motion.
But see, then I, then I, this is what I say,
no matter what I think of the little circle on my TV
that says J-O-E with the little,
that little face on there on the screen.
Here's what I want to say about you.
Chew.
Here's what I want to say about Chew.
I want to say this to you for the,
all the bad and the nasty shit you say,
I say you do, you said some really cool stuff
about psyche, our friend here,
and you added in and you were complimentary
and you let your little belly show.
You're a little soft underbelly even if like you think you're not like I didn't say you're gay
But you even kind of flirted in a funny way, and you weren't like all like weird
So there's a lot of good to you my friend. There's a lot of good
So I have to give you grace for that. You understand me even though like you're
Always remember to wipe from front to back all right
see that's love now a my a a salute sister p thank you and joe thank you for allowing yourself
to be such a dick that i let myself let alexandra
Alexandra in tonight because trust me I probably wouldn't have and I hi buddy
See you're good people. You just start a little messed up. It's all good. I forgive you too
Be nicer be nicer
be nicer. You haven't s
I'll talk all I want coz
a tongue. What do you thi
I love you too. No, I do. And Alexander, she's cool. And Joe, you're good. Okay. Two. I know
you're just insecure and you're deflecting. Don't worry, buddy. We see you. We love you anyway.
It's okay. Come out of the closet, bro. Just kidding. I'm so kidding. All right. Gotta go.
I got to play my card very early. Why are you an animal? Okay. You're an animal. All right. I
All right, all right, peace out you guys really by the way, there's four squares. I don't know if Brady Bunch Hollywood squares
Whatever you want. You want to sing a tune the Brady
What do you want to sing before I go
Good night, Irene. Good night, Johnny Boy.
Hey, have you seen the schoolhouse theme song?
Good night, though, good son. Alex, stop that, Ella.
Oh, buddy, can't you just, can you just, all right, all right, all right, we're going
to the next chapter, wait, second first, same as the first, um, Henry, the eighth, I gotta
go fight.
You're every day.
No, you fucking fat king.
Oh, come on.
Joe, you know what, Joe, you met your match, she can out talk you and that's good.
I mean, it's like J and J. O. It's it's conducive to be a conversationalist. I'm a J, you know,
and I'm the only J my parents have. You are. That's true. Go ahead. We'll talk to Alexander
All right, let's talk to Jamie. Oh, Jamie in the job. Okay. Go ahead. I'll be I'll be back in a few minutes. Okay
You got to take a big
Don't be don't be disgusted. Well, I have to do something and that's all you need to know
They're all my tests. Oh
Joe
What could I say one say the journey?
Sometimes I thank God for unanswered prayers
Just because I call Janey a whore doesn't mean I don't care
Just be good whenever somebody said to me. Why do you like so I guess that you know what motherfucker?
I don't like Suggie. I love Suggie. He's a best friend to me. Oh, thank you. Don't you ever ask me why it's all
Thank you. You know what? I love I love the people that love me, you know
Yeah, and I do love the people and even if they do some people that hate me. I
Still love because you know, I'm a loving person
I don't really have room for hate,
but it's like there's some people that have done some,
like a poor bum in my show are telling people
to like not go to my show or like, you know,
that I'm like a piece of garbage or whatever,
which has been said more than a few times recently.
You know, I will still forgive those people because I'm a forgiving person and I don't have
If I think about who do I hate? I really just don't hate anybody. I like I love
People and I see people are are very different and and
You're 45 so you hate him. Okay, but can I get I don't know did you see that you see the video with Q and I?
We have there's a there's a fantasy video. I want to show you real quick. This is all he's having sex with you
Yeah, no, he did he's not having sex with me, but he but she didn't make a video
I do want to share her video and everyone's subscribed to IPTV.
Let me see it. Let me see it.
Yeah, have you seen it yet? You haven't seen it yet. Okay.
No, I haven't seen it. Please show it if you don't mind.
This is called Join the Colt, okay? This is called Join the Colt, okay?
And here, Alexandra made this and she's very talented and there's a lot of details in this.
More than you would even know. Here you go. And enjoy this, everybody.
Yeah.
Let me enjoy it for a second.
Said he could see me.
Before I even spoke
I don't know about that, but I'm still here
All right, that's it, that's what I'm gonna do.
you said join the girl no feeling no crashing just getting closer to your own center to talk
they'll judge but what's that worth when you ain't even living in your own world
join the girl no shame no hiding no more running no more divided
come see me don't overthink it but i freeze every time i get close to the edge of it because the
world's got opinions on what this means and i don't even know what i'm thinking maybe it's more than
illusion something about you got me crushing in conclusions every symbol every line you draw
feels like truth i've been running from and the voices in my head keep telling
Where is it?
Shed it in!
Why does it feel like you have a boner?
You have a boner.
more living like I'm fading join the call your life your direction no more mass no more protection
let them say let them say what they want you don't know them the person you're not
join the call keep your heart evolving every step forward means a solve and everything they
told you to hold you find yourself when you join the call
I made
not something written
who the hell is this
let's find out
is that Joe Chidley
who is that
what the fuck
jokers alive
holy shit we're good to see you joker
I thought you were 10 bro
But you know
After a good time stop dreaming. I thought you disappeared from
There that's the way they were
So nice any Joker could have like one of my headphones is broken joker could have left me along
I think he still wants to come up and you're so well, there's an open invitation if you need to move in in some place
You're the only person I would let move in. You know. All right, Saki
Yeah, okay, don't do it
I know, I'll sit on that couch. You can take the bed joker, you know, really
You can live with me. You can live with me. Calm down, Saki. Wow. Okay. I'm gonna shut up. I'm gonna shut up. Okay. I'm so sorry
Man, don't shut up. Just shut your dick off. You know what I'm talking about right now
You know what I'm smoking dude. I'm smoking OG Skywalker. Oh, that sounds
Well, it's basically weed. It's basically you're smoking weed dumbass. I don't care if you call it Darth Vader. It's weed
Well, I was smoking Darth Vader
No, you're smoking. We're not running poison isn't running for me. I'm not Darth Vader. It's og skywalker
I was smoking c3pu
Oh my god, it's og skywalker dude
Look what I got dude. Oh, what's in there? Apple juice in a bottle. Wow, you got apple juice in a bottle.
I'm going to bring it over right now. That's family apple juice in a piss. That's piss. Actually that was piss.
It's not open. It's not open. Have you ever seen beat as a asshole?
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Damn
But like sucky's the only gay guy that gets in no ass like the niggas gay
I don't want anybody but Joe. What is that? What are you rubbing?
Hey guys, you know by the way, it was be this birthday. I do want to like I do have a happy birthday surprise for Vita
I mean, what is it? What's the prize? What's the present? Okay. Hold on. One second. I got it.
Go ahead. Show her. Give her a little birthday. This is my happy this is my happy birthday to
beta. All right. Okay. I got it. I got it guys. Are you ready? Here it is. Happy birthday beta.
Happy 51 beta. This is for beta's birthday.
Hey everybody, she's over half a century old, Vita's over half a century.
When he's around, she can't help but shout out.
He loves that beat.
It's all she wants.
You're the best.
The one she can't deny.
He's the reason for that sparkle in her eyes.
Damn it, Allison, we're not gonna start.
That's good enough!
That's good enough.
Is that really true?
Yeah.
Is that why she had that sparkle in her eye?
I thought we were good.
You were good.
Is that why she had the sparkle in her eye?
There she is. Beedah. Kiss that chicken, baby.
Is this true?
Yeah, that's got a little anso around that little head.
Yeah, it's not a blood, it's kind of sexy actually.
Beedah exposed.
Well, she is 55 years old. Happy birthday, happy 75th birthday.
Imagine being in Hamway to 100, Bina. You're Hamway to 100, you old whore. Sorry about that.
Yeah, so Joe shittley. How are you doing Joe shittley? I'm doing it now that I see you
I've literally thought you were dead. You're gonna see a big dog. You're like a ghost
What happened a good time a little wake
He's in jail for the how long
Bad Ashley you fat fuck in jail. He's in jail. He's in jail
Not till tomorrow when you guys are close. Not till tomorrow
It's going to jail.
Then it'll be a jail.
Why is he going to jail, dude?
Because he had the drive to that gas station on Easter.
Give it.
Whoa!
That's tequila.
Oh, my God.
Tequila shot.
All he wanted was one little Easter beer.
Just one little Easter beer.
And the cops were stalking him.
The cops were stalking him.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
You little soulmate.
Nice soulmate.
You know you are always nice to me like I mean you didn't need you didn't need to be you could have been mean to me
You could have been like some kind of like most of these straight got assholes, right?
But you were actually a kind guy you've also told all your stories on the chat even if they're embarrassing
Guys this has a really good his name is mr. Extendo XT and do I just want to say it's like general costors grandchild
I've been doing streams lately. They've been getting a lot of you. So at least I yeah, yeah
Guys if you over in his streams, he he'll play your song requests and stuff like that. He doesn't even charge for I mean is a
I
Once and I felt gayer than ever when I went to a show
No
Everybody
that's
But, you know, I was under it is bringing that word back because, you know, some people do deserve that word, you know, and so it means and it's I don't think I don't think black people deserve that word, but some people do, you know, and so this is a word.
You're right.
You're a nigger.
Oh, my God, psyche.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my gosh.
Did I say it?
You are racist son of a bitch.
Oh my gosh. Oops. Oops. I did it again. Right. Even say wasn't that racist.
Assume me. Okay, Britney Spears. Hey, Joker. Do you like my new tattoo, Joker? Do you like my new tattoo?
Yeah, sure. Nice nipples. Nice nips.
There you go. Hold on. I do get a new tattoo. Here we go.
It said fuck. Go ahead and show them. Fuck BKJ. Show them.
Hold on. Let me go over there. Here we go.
We'll take your shirt off.
You'll take it, guy.
I mean, you're already gay, you should just take your shirt off.
I'm so gay, here we go, here we go.
Here we go.
Here it is, like, you're already gay.
Take a look at that.
Ooh.
You like that?
There you go.
Ooh, that's cool.
Thank you so much.
I love it.
I love it, too.
Yeah, you're working out, Suggie.
You're working out, big dog.
Remember Joker when he when he did the he flexed for me. Yeah, I know I I've been the Auschwitz
I'm in the Auschwitz workout program. You know, yeah, it's working out. I love you. Sorry everybody, but here we go
Can I remove that they can't
I may have them because you fuck but uh
Okay, but anyway, that is my tattoo and
You know pages there a page page come on talk to the Joker come on come on on page if you can come up come on
Come on. I don't think you guys have talked to each other since you drew that picture of you. He has a crush
I know he's a crush look at his face. He's turning red. No
And I tell you my theory about Perry page. Yeah, that's my theory. I think she's like
like a cart girl that drives the beer around and I think that's why she's an alcoholic because she
tried oh come on Joe come on I'm sorry I'm sorry don't say that don't say that but you know what
I love you know Brandon can say stuff about people and then it's like and then it's like and then
Paige is like I don't fucking care like she really doesn't she pages like this kind of I don't give
with like you know when all else they'll just go in on joker when all else now it's just
all this is cool as fuck pages like stay with me since the beginning like really every like
when everyone else loved me joker's still here joe's still here and page is still here and uh i
really appreciate you guys i like you know what it might sound gay but i love sucky dude he's my
I would have started streaming on this channel. So I
Started streaming on like this the cult or the cult of psyche, which was called psyche awakens at the time
Yeah
Seriously fuck Christine that old bitch. I mean seriously. I'm not not to like say anything about anybody
But yeah, she's like she's like she's like, oh, I know her feels blah blah blah. You can't come up. Okay, Paige
Well, Paige, can you send Joker some love?
Because I remember when he drew you and your neck was like this long.
It was like as long longer than my neck.
Yeah, yeah, if you kind of like this, I don't know, my neck long enough.
You know, you with like a giraffe neck and these earrings, that was Joker.
Oh, you're drawing. I want to draw Joker right now. I'm going to have a no pet out.
All right, can I say something? There was one video on the page.
All right, bye, you gay guys. Shut up, you gay. Shut up, you gay guy.
There was one time Paige was like going live on the ball court. She had these little tiny
Daisy Dukes. So, and I was like, I need to watch this video. 10 more. 10 more.
Daisy Dukes? What did the page have to have for her?
I didn't say anything. So oh yeah, I didn't hear that
Say it again Joe Shippley
Not gonna repeat myself. I bet you won't I bet you won't say I'm trying to wear these little stores
And she was like, oh you will be to serve you a drink as they serve me three of them bitch
Joke I'm drawing you right now. Here we go
Draw Joker just draw a cigarette draw a gay guy with like a
Your general cluster general cluster and it will look like joker's granddad. I have joker's picture. Here's joker. Are you ready?
I already drew it. Here's what we see. Well, we can see it right now, but show his picture. Oh my god
Are you showing you he's showing you to psyche he showed a picture of you. Was that me? Oh my god. Yeah
I'll pay for the shipping for that. Okay
That is awesome. Yeah, I'll buy that. I'll have to.
I'll put it over my TV so I can do it more.
How much do you want to pay? I'll pay $30 for that. Oh my god. We're doing a bidding war. Okay. Well, the joke
You can send me I'll pay for the shipping
Doesn't mean I'll send you the mount for the shipping. Okay. I imagine how much sand name will paper beat his stinky old panties
Oh my god, is that Joker? Yeah, I brought his nose. Hold on. I gotta do his nose. Hold on. It's a guy
All right, God now I got it
I gotta go to bed after this cigarette.
It's like, hey, bro, I have to turn my sick camera.
There you go, there you go, there you go.
Gotta have to go to tea, too.
Also need this one. You want this one, too? Also need this one. Yes. I want that. What the fuck is that? Oh my god
That's my cutie. Oh that was Joker. I'm sorry. I don't know. I thought it was him
I was at the show the broke my bounce it again because you know
No, no, no. Yeah. Well, yes. Yes. Yes. I mean because you know Joker and I in the summertime we actually ran out here
We were actually so happy to see Joker stop making him. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you
Anyone Joker I wouldn't do anything for you like really the Joker really is basically my father into the community because
he was the one that you're like a father. He's like a father figure. He said, psyche,
here's how to start streaming. And Benny would even give me this information,
but Joker, Joker gave me the information to start and go following and stuff like that.
Benny didn't even do this. Benny was, I don't know if Benny was like, whatever, but, but,
uh, he was gatekeeping. He was gatekeeping, but, but I do have this thing to show you guys.
This is this is this is called true romance. This is what happens when I know I love real people fall in love
This is this is a real thing right here
Here we go
Sikes pussy is compulsive
well since we're gonna be working together there it is breaking it's time we start drinking it
what's what is this my pussy
yeah your asshole is uh perky perky perky perky ladies
oh it's like when i come to call you
do you know somebody named jack where he was fishing buddies
You want me to take my shirt off?
No, we're just fishing, bud.
We're just fishing, bud.
You know, it could be like this.
Just like this always.
We're not dead.
We're just fishing, bud.
We're told this is the wrong place.
And we're dead.
We're wrapped up.
Of course, you're found a way to make the 10th best of dear.
But you don't go up there to fish.
You don't know nothing about it.
It's nice.
I've never seen you like this.
No!
I'm asked to see my wear and I'm assured.
You have no idea how bad it gets if you can't fix it. You've got a standard. I wish I knew how to quit you
It's the best
I never seen you so happy before, she's like, where's that, I've never seen that smile before in my life.
I've never seen you so happy, Jurgert.
You're not Jurgert, like, Saggy, you're really happy.
I was, I was just fucking around, dude, I was just fucking around.
I know, I, guys, it's completely...
They edited it so well though, they edited it so well.
That was a trip kick video, that was really good.
I don't want to quit you.
They edited it so where it makes me look like it was like a compilation of like four different or five
Remember cuz you said you didn't want to see her bussy
Cry I think in one shot. That's actually pissed. It's actually piss
You know drunk that piss
Whoa, I'm getting drunk tonight guys. Whoo. Oh, yeah
Hey, I guess it was hair my chest. I think I
I don't want to quit psyche. I don't want to quit it. Let's crack it. I'm in here. Hey guys
This is the best one you if you haven't noticed if you haven't noticed this is just like a whole mess of
Abwatches, though. Are you drunk?
It is to kill it in there it is to kill it in there look at this ball the key like
Wedding
I can't drink it. Oh, I mean I have to drink it with a lot of apple juice
I don't know. I'll get a drug as fuck.
The first one was in the middle of nowhere. He was on the street, like a band in the street on escape room, right?
And then he was on the band street on the skateboard.
I was like, this guy is so cute and funny and cool.
And then he talks to me.
He's so cute.
He had an Indian friend and his Indian friend and he was like lifting weights in the backyard
I was like, can you guys do a flex show?
And they took up their shirts and they started flexing it for me and I was like, okay
I mean then you jerked off and then you jerked off
I would love to rub it
Remember your Indian friend that came over and you were flexing in the backyard with me?
It really was Karthik.
His name was Karthik, the Indian.
Yeah, the Indian guy.
That was awesome.
Like, really.
And you flexed for me.
You took off your shirts and you were like,
I mean, I wasn't having, I wasn't having, I still didn't have it.
And Joker's like, Joker, I'm sorry, I don't want to embarrass you or anything, but you're
a really-
I'm sorry about that, Joker.
You're a really cute guy, Joker, and I'm sorry.
I wouldn't go back.
I wouldn't say so.
So, Joker, if you ever need anywhere to stay in California, I'm not, I'll, you take the
bedroom and you can lock the door and stuff like that.
You could always go straight to hell.
So you'd always go straight to hell.
if you want joker so you need to drink some more tequila so i know i do i do but joker i'm
saying it's worse i don't know i don't know
i don't know
it gets me or something hey but you're not a shantlank but it's a piss
by the way
I want you guys joker. Are you my mod? You're a mod of mine, right? If you're not just come in the chat
I'll make you a mod. I want you to put I'm sorry, but I do have trolls and stuff
But everyone here tonight. I don't think I've hidden in one person tonight. I think everyone
I think everybody respectful and they say I think others I the trash took itself out of my chat, you know
And I think I just have good people here
you know, I'm so tell joker what you want in the duty you tell joker what you want in the duty
I whatever he wants to do he wants to tie me up and I would let him I would let him have a
joker you want to have a fantasy or are you just like you know you can't put me in 20 yes I know
I love whatever you want to do whatever he wants to do whatever his fantasy is I will make his fantasy come true
I'm crawling to bed.
I'm trying to crawl upstairs to bed.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I went too far.
Okay.
I always go too far.
But Joker, if you want to, like, for me in a suitcase and 25 pieces, I probably let you.
Yeah, like, if you're a single jugger, psyche, if you're a single psyche, what's the say-lo song to you?
Oh my god. Joe you made it weird. Joe. Why did you make it weird?
No I did not. I did not make it weird. I just want to hold you Joker.
That was good. Did I say that? Oh my gosh. No I just didn't say that I made it up.
I am fucking embarrassed now. Wow. Joker I'm sorry. Joker it was a joke Joker. Joker I can take a dick you can take a joke right?
Okay, did I see that out?
Help me, I said that out loud.
Yes, you said it out loud.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Why do I do that?
Why is Jurgers so goddamn sexy?
I don't know! I don't know!
I don't know, but there's just something about it.
I'm 26 years old. I'm gone. I'm gone.
I'm gone, guys.
How old are you?
How does he know his age?
Guys, cancel Psyche.
Dude, hashtag cancel Psyche.
I know. During the Kate, hey, Kevin.
By the way, Kate.
I know you donated thousands of dollars a day.
Don't stop denying it.
You know, either way.
Oh, they should really, they can't
actually donate this, is that true?
Well, thousands of dollars.
And if it's either Barry's money or Kate's money,
yeah, thousands of dollars.
When that Kate's fat fucking ass,
then Kate's fat fucking pig ass wants to judge you
because you have Brandon up here
when she donates to you at all.
Exactly, exactly.
Exactly, that's the point I was going to make.
But somebody liked my post and everyone liked her post.
you know I guess I'm just shit and stuff like that but you know what case
Brandon is socially awkward person but Brandon's on a bad guy and he's been also like bullied harass
slandered and stuff like that and so I understand the psc of the situation and even even like you
know gamble was saying well you know what we just call everybody everybody that has anything
It's like, don't that fact, don't, don't that fact that Sam and judge you for talking to Brandon? Don't he don't, don't
And technically if Sam and if Sam is supports a and beta tells the same and that beta you're a pedophile protector to you
Right. And so it's cage. She's doing any thousands of dollars today. I mean, it's like
She's gonna die
He already said that Brandon said, well, I'm saying that, but it's like, you know, Zaya,
I guess he would be considered a febophile or there's a different definition. I think pedophile
is a word that you use on people that are after children and stuff like that. And people want
to put it so broadly on everybody.
And you know at the 17 and younger now people like Bita and Christine have ruined this community
People like Bita and Christine have fucking ruined this entire community
It used to be fun up here
Then you got people like Bita and Christine like what the fuck happened to this fucking community
All right, I mean he was under 21. Yeah, yeah, she did that is true
Was he legal drink? No, so she took a person that was 19 years old and bought him alcohol. 17 is considered underage
Is 17 considered a child
Are we gonna put it?
Retard listen you could never say that to be that cuz she would kick you off a string you could never say beta
Why'd you buy an underage kid drinks? Oh, you're out of here, Sam. Oh shoo-loo-loo-loo-loo beta
You're a fucking loser just like every one of us. Don't act like you're better. Not a fucking drunk or
He was 19. I know he was 19, but yeah, she how old was she 39 or something at the time?
Right. Exactly. Yes. At least 20 years older than him, at least 20 years older.
Yeah. If it was me, she's by him alcohol, because this fucking whore can't get funk.
She has my 90 year old kid alcohol, because this whore can't get fucked.
Like, Bita, you're a loser, bro. You're trying to fucking 90 year old kid, because you can't get
dick. Because nobody wants to fuck your ex-husband. Then you get divorced three times or something like
Like they do you know what I think the husband's Mary Bita and then when they find like God this lady's manipulative
I can't stand this bitch. They're like I gotta get out of here at the worst this work. No wonder. She's been forced twice
Or I'm bad for a show because I tell the truth and it's like she's afraid of the truth exactly. Yeah
I was 19 and so someone's 17 and 364 days. Is that a big difference between 17 and so
it's like what if you say how one second from being 18 then they would say oh that's a pedophile
is that that makes sense and you know it's funny even cheetah wouldn't fuck her even cheetah was
like i'm fucking this old lady nobody was the fuck you beat her nobody cares about your old pussy
nobody cares about your old indian pussy you understand
right. She's not Indian. She's a Persian. Oh Sam, what kind of a Sam man does? I mean
one person. Oh yeah. We all saw Samman and Bita when they were playing their Eugeo game.
Do we see, do you sell this Joe right? This is when they're playing Eugeo together. I
do see it. Let me see it one more time. Refresh my mind. Refresh my mind. Refresh my mind. Yeah
I'm gonna refresh your mind. This is Samman and Bita. Thank you. Playing Eugeo. Okay. Thank
you. That's it.
You see that's it. That's like Ziya. All right
Looks like Mimi
It doesn't always understood the same thing. It's like Tracy. It looks like Tracy
You ever notice what Bita never even knows nobody. I love you. I love you. Like you don't even fucking know him
Oh, no, no, everyone at first, but then she turns on them. Exactly. She loves that. I love you. I love you
Oh, and did you see Kate? There's careless Kate. Oh
Oh my god, stop it. Damn it. That's not what he is. Her name is Big Ben. That's her. I mean it looks like her. It sounds like her. It smells like her, but I don't think it's England.
I mean, is that literally her I mean with the put away I mean it does look like
I think Shrek's mind in a way, but yeah, I love you
Yeah, oh and she's so holier than that. Oh, oh my god. Well, you psyche you're protecting a predator. Well, you know what?
I remember though. I'm not you not to interrupt you. I apologize. I didn't mean to interrupt you
But the first time Kim was ever here Peter was like, I love you and I just said to Kim
Like she don't even fucking know you and she loves you like this is the kind of people are down with
Like they don't even know you but I love you. I love you. It's Peter
you're half a century old nobody cares about your old ass shut up and then you clear my
chat out real quick so i'm going to show you a video you're watching this video real quick okay
Bruce show it to me
i already love it i already love it
Just this hour at the table
Turn it up a little bit
Brantons
Just whatever's true to say
I built a council at a coding crown
emoji at the end of broken things no green check mark when the gateways
cracked no all systems nominal and the systems leaking just the truth and what
you do with that I'm the messenger
friend of me you have a witness not a daughter not a priest not a prayer just a
chair outside the frame and the love that says I'm not lying when I tell you I'm
there they think Greg Gregor needs ritual the daughter needs the song the
family needs to be real I'm too belong I need none of that I need the pack the
love between us doesn't have to act you call just I'm tired I call the work I've
Not warmer than the others, not colder either
Adjacent awake, the breath between two breathers
You asked me how I was feeling
I told you the truth
Nobody, no tomorrow
You asked me anyway
No tomorrow
new trials watching a good vlog
That was fucking awesome, whatever song that was.
I had that video.
I do.
I like the hands in it.
I liked how you had the digital hand.
And what looked more like a physical hand.
It was kind of like a hand theme.
But I like the go with that song, that song.
It's a little handsy.
That song's a little handsy.
I want to be able to handle it with you, Joe.
But by the way, I'll say.
You have a type.
I was watching you talking to Joker.
So you have a type, because I didn't realize it
until looking at Joker just now.
Joker and Q have a similar look and a...
In a little bit
Like the same goatee
Like he was a little bit too mainstream joker has interesting eyes. He has very um
Sort of
in very kind eyes too, even though he can be a certain way.
He's mischievous.
Yeah, and I like the mischievous guys.
I mean, and it's a joke, we're 26 years old
and people are, people are saying I'm a PDF because-
He's only 26?
Really?
He's 26 years old, yeah.
He's 26.
What?
He's just been online a long time you know the young guys who have been around since they were like
You know like 20 or something. I always forget how young they are because it's
Yeah
They are they're 20s and stuff and it's like and not not that if they I ever been in real life
You know, I would respect their boundaries and all that kind of thing like really it's like I'm not like
I play kind of a part on on YouTube where I say I maybe you just like younger men. It's okay. I mean, it's like, yeah
Okay, Hugh Hefner Hugh Hefner totally socially acceptable for him to be
However old he was you know 80s 70s 80s always with girls in their 20s nobody even
it became so mobilized
But you know
We don't really know who's behind some of these screen names. These might be some very conservative people
We don't know where they are
So, you know, you need to relax a little bit. Why are you so damn good-looking Alice? Like why are you so?
I'm a queen of lighting. I know my I know my colors. I know the lighting
Yes, yes, I am purple I thought was cool that
flirt is totally okay amongst adults. I do agree. I think if you're 20s, you're me 20s,
you're late 20s, I can flirt with you. I mean, I don't think, but people want to say you can
date younger guys if you want to, I would say don't go under 25. I think it's okay. He's 26,
Well, there you go. He's a rich. He's a perfect age. I don't know. Maybe I'm a pervert for that.
Okay. No, you're not. No, you're not. You're a youthful. You're very youthful. Okay. You're a
good guy. Sometimes people want to date somebody younger. Sometimes when I was in my 20s, I dated
late fifties
Wow
I mean, it's that's what it just depends on where you're I mean in some countries. That's very normal
Most sexy guys. I ever I ever hooked up with was in his like almost 60 years old, you know, and it's like
He was a Mexican game member.
I thought I'd make some AI as some of these after most of you.
Got you.
I got you.
I'm going to.
The psyche years in prison.
I got to go to jail for like three hours. Seriously. I was in a shower. I'm an old. I'm an old
hag. I'm an old because when I'm 50, I'm just stopping. I'm not going to get any older. I'm
just that's going to be it. So, you know, I'm thank you. I appreciate that.
by the way Alex you are you're a gorgeous woman and it's like you're gorgeous i think you like
you stopped aging probably 10 years ago so sometimes i have got a sexy woman on this earth god
like god put alex here as long as there's lighting
filters, technology, cosmetic surgery, makeup.
What else do I need?
Just whatever I can get.
I'm grabbed.
Whatever you can grab.
But you know, Alice is a gorgeous woman.
And it's like, seriously,
I don't ever want you to like ever die yourself because.
Not even gorgeous like, you know, physically, but like, you know, her spouse or her teeth are perfect
I'll give her credit. Her teeth are
No, no, no, no, no from here. They are from here. They look like it. Yeah. Well, I have them. They're they're in my mouth
Do they hurt? Do they get sore?
No, do my teeth get sore? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
intergenerational dating, because we're already on that topic.
That's on the road, guys.
Yes, thanks.
It's a show.
Joe, have you ever had a bisexual experience, Joe?
I want to hear a show.
Sorry, but I want to tell you one thing.
I didn't want to bring...
I had sex two nights ago with a sweet woman.
I didn't really want to bring this up,
because I really don't want to bring her up on this panel.
But yes, I've been having sex very recently.
Big dogs.
So, is that your question?
No, I'm asking if there's a guy involved.
I mean, any guy. Oh, yes, yes, yes. Yes. There was two guys above that. Oh my God. Oh my God.
No, I'm not going to tell you about it. Okay, so Joe is in a foursome or something like that. Okay.
Grow up, Saige. Grow up. Okay. Okay.
Well, you know what? I would like to be in a four or something, but, you know, I haven't
been in a six or something. I really am like a brood. Here's my thing.
We've got to get you laid, Psyche. I know. Let's do it.
On Grindr last year, I, like, I borrowed a government house and he's like, oh,
call the gig guys you know, and I want to sell a little GHB and meth to them. And I was like,
I mean, so this is and I was like, can you please leave and then he left and I mean that was that was the night
I mean, it's like are you wearing a necklace sounds or is that it looks like you're right?
Yeah, I am so sexy where you're laying. You look so damn sexy
Might have turned you on a little bit is that what happened the BBC dance video
Oh, yeah, you're right. That's what it was. Oh my God. Is that the gurney's coin? Is that the gurney's?
Can you see the guy?
It's like Joker.
Oh, that's a Joker coin.
Maybe Joker, and it has one banner right there.
It's exactly like Joker.
Yeah, we have another guy.
Wait, wait, turn it around. Let me see the picture.
That's like a song dog.
Yeah, the back of it is Hebrew letters.
Let me see the other side.
And the other side is this one.
Here we go
Well, you know that video I mean, I've never seen that before that's interesting I
Kind of your rut because I didn't know that was on the backside of your medallion. I did not know that
This is all the first the first
Horns on your head without me knowing that yeah
Did you implant that in my mind? You might have I don't know, but that's the earth angel right there
He's gonna send off on or you know more
Really
Translate to on the back
Angels and so they took like I think out of like
Exodus or something like that the Moses Moses and they found 72 names
All of them are three Hebrew letters each
And they made 72 angels and so if you look going to Kabbalah, there's 72 angels with that with that's wild to me because the music video
I made that join the video. I put the heat. I put the horns on your head and it looks like that image
I
Think it does. Oh my god. I don't look exactly. Oh my
Yes, it does. Yes. Yes, you're you're
Doing we can see your horns. We can see your horns like it. We can see
Look, I got it. I'm gonna put it up to the camera. Is that sure?
that's gold. Yeah, well, that's
it was made of pure gold. But
yeah, he does have horns. And
this is like an installment has
I think there's several sigils
there's every planet. There's
about three angels, or three,
three, three sigils per planet.
And so I like your cross
necklace. And that's a little
cross necklace. I say I think
that's sexy. I always wear a
cross. Yeah.
There you go. Well, you're
looking very good tonight.
And a cross is a very beautiful symbol as well.
Some people will say negative things about it, but I think the cross is basically what
we are.
We are like, we have these arms.
And the and we're going to reserve is dire. Yes, that's what you gave me something to research in regards to the 72 angels of the shim
Hemaphore raw. Yeah, shim hemphorage. It was just like the yeah
Okay, shimphorage with the cabala. I'm looking it up. Yeah, celestial beings derived
It's like psyche didn't know my birthday was coming up, but psyche said to be like
I didn't have a birthday.
It's like he's like a brother to me.
When is your birthday?
It's like, what's your birthday?
What's your birthday, Joe?
None of your business, but listen to me a birthday. I'll read about your birthday real quick
He might not want it cuz he's
June second I'll make it June second. Okay, you're seven two a seven two. That's 72 angels
I also I mean I want to give too much away, but I'll say seven two is an important number to me
Well, I just think it's interesting that you have that image on the back of that amulet
and i mean that's what i made in the video and i did not know that you had that on that
medallion amulet thing yeah and that's the first the first um the first salman seal the sun
and that's that one and i also have salman seals of jupiter uh and saturn and uh
they they are have you ever seen me be masters quads like you give me the amulet
never do you remember the Fred Savage movie was called monsters or something that was that Fred Savage
stop it you know that's my favorite movie you're trying to trick me you know i love little monsters
stop little monsters Fred Savage is my best movie so these are the angels of the cabala
actually my favorite movie is called little six i don't uh i don't pray to the cabala
Okay, well say oh wait wait say say you're just ruining these are always right. Yeah, you're really well
It's all all the all the religious for the most part everything is linked together. I mean as I learned these things
I'm open to learning about them because I feel like I'm still in the Old Testament of the Bible.
So in a way it does relate, but I didn't know about this. This is interesting. I'd like anything to do with spirituality, especially if I don't know about it.
It's a pleasure to be up here with psyche analysis like two of my best like I'm up here surrounded by two my best friends
your apple juice today. Okay, I'm on it. I'm on the opposite end from you right now because I
have some coffee. So I'm just like, I'm super like, you know, and you're having fun.
I'm having fun tonight because you know, it's like, I've been like really like pretty sober
lately and having some silver streams. You have been
yeah and they've been not advanced like yeah they've been trying
you're good Marcy Marcy says her half sister kimberley hold on uh from oh my god somebody's
old or crazy she's her probably her father passed away 2002 at theta 659
and your sister is almost 59.
Yeah, there's coincidences.
Like you have to look into all these numbers
and things like that.
I didn't read that, I didn't read that.
I made, I re-pinned that so I can read it.
I won't read it out loud, but I'll read it to myself.
I love you guys, by the way.
I'm gonna turn something into a comment again.
You guys, sometimes it takes courage to be your friend.
And I know Alex sometimes says the same thing.
It's like it takes courage to be your friend sometimes
because people are just such followers
and afraid to like,
based on truth, and they wanted to join the popular bandwagon.
That's right, that's right.
It's because, you know, Alexandra speaks a lot of truth.
Like, she really does, and if she makes a mistake along the way,
or if she, she'll admit it, and she'll, I mean, she'll say it.
She was awesome.
She did say it today.
Like, she did say it today, like, or yesterday.
And she said-
She's sexy.
Maybe there was a mistake about Zaya, or, you know, and it-
Go ahead and say as a complex. That's a very complex situation. Now, we do know
What's huge that's questionable, but we also know or
There's things that we don't know and see he's a tough one to read because
He has so many barriers up because he has been through a lot in his life
He can be mean. He does not always think he has low impulse control, but I think people do
take advantage of that within him to kind of weaponize him in a way. But then he allows himself
to be weaponized. Right. That's he's he's a he's a little bit of a tough case to really examine.
She does well, I did they're okay, but he wants people to know
About him, but he doesn't know how to and then he's got all these
Barriers around him in the form of people who want to keep him to themselves
It's he's he's a heart. He makes his own life difficult
but
You know, I feel I just feel like if I didn't if I hadn't done if I hadn't said a couple things today
It would forever bother me
I I don't want to talk directly to him, but I know he listens to my streams, you know
and I said what I needed to say and
I'm at peace with it. Yeah, and I think I did the right thing and I do want to say like I hope so you shut down the
rumor pedo website today. Yes. Yes, and
Because we know
There's somebody that has been trying to
Profile of stuff as a pedo hunter and stuff like that
Actually like now certain things are clicking in my mind when it comes like at least a year ago, maybe longer
Zaya did a stream in regards to quote unquote pedo hunters
and he was talking about myself and Ganville.
And I was like, why are you lumping me with Ganville
in this?
Now I'm wondering something.
I'm just wondering some things about Ganville.
I'm not going to accuse, but I am going to document
as I do.
Just going to build a little documentation.
I think he's a bratty bully.
That's what I think.
And it's like, you know, to think that's the way to get cloud nowadays is because it's such an unpopular topic or such a popular, maybe a popular topic to demonize and you can say just like, you know, oh, I saw your song by the way demonize demonitize that was right.
And I was demonetized in a way and then YouTube wants to put ads in my videos now after they
did. I never had ads in my videos before. Now they want to put ads on it, right? After
they demonetize me. It doesn't seem very fair. I don't care if YouTube, I don't give a fuck
about YouTube.
You need to go ahead and create your merch, meaning your merchandise. I think it's time
for you to do that because people would purchase it.
That is so cool to have a psyche t-shirt. Hell yeah.
Yeah.
And like I said, I live into the site of thongs, or my era thongs.
Yeah. I mean, really, it's like, I've been so demonized. Like, really, all I had on my channel,
that was monetized was the membership. You never did nothing wrong.
And it's like, maybe they put thumbnails up that are AI thumbnails. Anybody that uses any AI?
They're going to try to demonetize right now when they're encouraging AI use with their
they have AI tools of their own excuse for them to take out whoever they want to take
out.
Yeah.
You know, meaning.
White out.
I'm really.
Channel.
Would you have the sexiest legend on YouTube up here like Alex like, come on, I know.
Alexander is the sexiest legend up here.
Smile, Alex. Come on, give us a little smile.
Jesus, give us a smile.
Oh, there it is.
Alexander is gorgeous.
My screenshot of that, actually.
Alex, I'm really just like, I'm really humbled.
Jesus.
I love you Alex. I love you too Psyche.
All I want to say about it is I love you and it's like there's a lot of people that want to
destroy, try to destroy and like come between us but yeah I think we understand each other.
We're the same birthday, you know, you know Alexander and I are the same birthday January, and I say one
Like when beta talks the same as she don't even like Sam and like really deep down be do it. Oh, I think he does
I think
They are dating they are dating. They're eating. They're eating. Oh my god. I'm mad
Imagine that imagine dating that
Oh, okay. Hey, no, I know I know it's Joe, but let's not even get into that. I don't want to know. I think that
Number one if it's her birthday today
Genuinely, I hope she has a birthday. You see
Very important. Happy birthday
Abby
This will be the year that she
Comes on camera. Oh, I love that you
Streams where she has come on camera before
She come on camera. I might show a few times. She should one time to dance in the window
She did dance in the dark and it's like it's like it's a little bit
Like it has me real dark. It has me really dark and no I can see her and then it's like in a camera
It's like we can't really see her like we actually saw her we all go
Yeah, she's she's blocking me in her chat and her and her and her
Panel so is crystal land and so is cave. Oh my she won't let me go anybody else
A lot of a lot of people are just such followers
Is really sad
It's so sad if you don't
But you know what they're doing
They're they're hoping that um
You put more importance upon them than you should okay exactly in the end
You're gonna end up more popular in the end. You're going to have the better
But but they're playing a game it's a mental game that they're playing with you
Don't don't don't let them play the game
Like you and me is that we don't give a fuck about the other people
We're gonna be ourselves, no matter what, right?
We're gonna be ourselfs, we don't care if we have
one person in the chat, 100 people in the chat,
we're gonna be ourselves and tell the truth.
That's what I love about you so much,
is that you tell the truth.
Even if we had a backtrack once in a while
and say, okay, well, I made the wrong judgment sometimes,
we're gonna tell the fucking truth.
Like yeah, that's what we stand up for but we're also gonna have fun and
A lot of this because here's here's here's what your advantage is psyche
I love you so the artistry. Okay. You're bringing a level of theater to the streaming
and I love it really, you're bringing some more than just drama, you're bringing some sophistication to it, you're creating like an organized show.
and that's what you want.
So, you know.
I mean, you should, I mean, you know these people.
Oh, I got some plans.
You haven't, I'm keeping a few things under wraps
that I'm working on.
It's gonna be a good year.
It will be.
And I'm really glad you're talking to Joni
because Joni's a good friend of mine.
Like, offshore.
I like talking to her.
She, she, she can read me very well, extremely well.
And that's awesome.
I liked it.
He's a good person and you're a good person.
I just know good people.
That's like what people say about me is like,
they say, oh, no one's supporting you anymore.
Well, I'm still one of the best people and the best people understand me and
We understand and it's like
I don't give a fuck love anything else about it. It's like I'm just thankful to have you as a friend
And I just want to thank
I'm in love with you sake
show. I was gonna say thank you for like everyone's everyone's trying to say like everyone meaning
the majority are trying to like demonize me demonize you and we're like really the truth
is we're good people we're good guys we're good guys. I found a list of these angels
Yeah, I found the list of them that their names
Yeah, you read the list please. Can you read the list?
Long of a list
You names, but but my personal birth angel if you can go to your birthday and find a yellow
Leila hell
Capricorn yeah
Pop that corn boy. Leila hell is Lilith. I mean it's like and so
Where the hell is that? Is it really? Yeah
Well, you know
Apparently, that's a spiritual challenge for me because I initially as you know, I had an aversion to it
now I'm open to it or her and
I'm I think I had an aversion because there's elements within myself upon learning about Lilith first off
I'm a little scared of myself sometimes and yeah, yeah, yeah, I am and it's just some
I guess it's some things within the description of Lilith that bothered me to an extent because
it's you know, things that
Maybe I don't like about myself very much or certain circumcised is the January 7th angel is Lila hell and
Your perfect hours. Don't you ever get down yourself and also, but you're a first woman to be demonized
And we you understand demonization. Oh, I definitely do
Yeah, I do and I don't
Hey, we're having a great conversation with guys. This is a conversation. You will not hear anywhere else
Like I promise you
Ask is her be the Sam and lover panel. You ain't gonna hear this conversation nowhere else
Just to be like I'm doing like research over here learning about this stuff
I mean see you give gifts of knowledge. That's a nice thing. I like that
Thank you. Thank you. He does. I'm not trying. I have no agenda. My agenda is the truth. Really? My agenda is the truth. And you're a very similar person. We're one on the same day. We're born two years apart. Exactly. The day of unusual interest. Yes.
My birthday is May thirty-third.
It's no May thirty-third, Joe.
Oh, damn it.
You actually mean the exact day, Joe.
I can read your birthday.
If I did have one birthday gift, I'd be like,
I want Alex for my birthday gift.
Would you like to know about your angel?
I want Alex all night long.
Joe, Joe, Joe.
Shut up for a second.
Okay, what's his birthday? He said he said what is it may I'm sorry?
Okay, Hariel is his angel Hariel h a r i e l
Yeah
Joe is is Hariel is the color of she does
Hariel by the way
I'll look up what Harry is about.
I never as much fun when I'm on suckies than anybody else.
Suckie, thank you.
Say, Harry-o, Angel.
Well, nice ass.
Nice ass, by the way.
Why don't you shake it?
Don't break it, big dog.
Okay, it's very God say Ariel represents the comforting God or save your God
associate it with your acquire and the dates June 1st through of June 5th
Ariel symbolizes purification moral innocence
Intellectual clarity
The tacos, what is it showing Alex? What is that dinner? Fuck you Joe shut the fuck up
He shoved that beat that your gullet sick
Double you
This angel helps to break addictions aligns
Morality and inspires artists and scientists
It's the 15th Kabbalistic Angel.
Trocotus.
Okay.
So interesting because Joe, you are very scientific in a way.
Like you are very...
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
You're very analytical.
You're very
No, it's like you're very loving and you know what?
I love that you set me as your best friend because you are my best friend
People tell me. Oh, why do you talk this like me? I'm gonna tell them. Fuck you all. It's like he's the best
That's what I'm gonna tell them next time. I know I'll say
You know, Joe, you're the best and always honors the best and sick really
I'm just I'm just blessed because guys you guys like
abandoned me and you didn't you could have gone because I abandoned you a
little bit
It's okay because you know what Alexander you and I had a little we had to have our
We had to have our our fight together, right? We had to have the fight. That's what made you guys friends
That's what strengthen your friendship. I think I really think I really think that I think it did
I I mean you let me hit you a lot. Thank you
You know, I went up against you too, you know, and I was
You can be a little mean. You're a little mean, but not too mean, not too mean.
No, I would never want to really hurt you.
And it's like, but, you know, I will, I'll spar and stuff like that.
But at the same time, I loved you this, I loved you all the way through.
I really, I loved her first.
I loved her first.
All right.
Now this angel for, um, you and I, psyche, um, you're right.
It can be pronounced lay a l L lay a l L.
Okay.
Symbolism, bravery, frankness, and intellectual capability is believed to help in overcoming
sadness and despair. Interesting, talisman. I wonder if there's pictures of these angels.
Yeah, I also need some spontaneously talk, Alex. It's so sexy just when you even say nothing.
When you say nothing
Joe I
Is who let who believe women should be seen and not heard always say that
Right, but he did say it in a smooth way you got to give him credit
I know but I don't talk to you and me right now. Okay. Thank you for forgiving me
Because well, thank you for forgiving me. Hey
Hey
We get each other. At the end of the day, I know we understand each other. At the end of the day, I know we're pretty evenly matched.
I think it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like a evenly matched thing where it's like, that's why we got over it.
Because it's like, none of us can overtake the other because I think we have similar minds.
Yeah, I don't think I like you. I didn't like fighting you. I didn't like it either, but you know what?
It needed to happen. It needed to happen
Just to show us
Well, you have to fight your friends sometimes. Yeah, and I really do appreciate you because it's like and you are a very fair person
And I'll say I mean it's like
Sometimes it if it's worth it, right if it's not worth it. No at the end of the day
For you to forgive Zia in a certain way
there's something around him that needs to be fixed.
And I can see it, but it's not for me to fix it.
I think it's just for me to point it out.
Right.
And, yeah, I guess.
There's been, he and I didn't always,
I wasn't always scared of him.
It had to do with a lot of external interference.
Um, some of the external interference came at me very aggressively and the external around
him does not want me to be friends with him.
And that's fine because I don't, I'm not going to make an effort.
Not where he's at in his life right now.
don't want to see him get in trouble unjustly or I don't I don't want to see
other people pull him into trouble because of whatever their you know agenda
or objective is exactly that's what I don't want for him but I think that he
is a selfish person and I think that he is a bit thoughtless and he needs to be
more thoughtful
And I'm not talking about myself I'm talking about others around him and he needs to be more
What's the word I want to use
He needs to use more discernment right
That's what I feel for Zaya. I would say
Zaya, I think you have another chance
and I think you have a chance to prove yourself
and I think you have a chance to show who you really are
beyond anything else.
And so Zaya, you know, be a better person.
Be a better person, don't fall into the traps
and don't fall into what said about you.
I think even the harshest critics about you,
or give me another chance and take this chance and do better.
I think he will.
I think that he just has to figure out where he's at
and he needs to,
you know how your friend, Joanie,
was talking a bit about forgiving and forgetting
when she was on here tonight?
From what I heard in his stream
He needs to even if he doesn't forget
Just for his own sake. I think he needs to forgive his grandma and his mom. I
think that would take a big amount of sadness off him and
Help him a little bit if he were to consciously do that
So yeah, I think you're being given another chance personally
I think you're being given another chance
And I would take that and I would run with it and I would
Don't double down on whatever
Negativity you're you're involved with I would say
you're being given another chance and take that and
I'll give you that.
I think Alexander will give you that.
And personally, I don't think you're a bad person.
And I don't think she does either.
I think that just go with the positive side of this.
Because I think everyone deserves a second chance.
And it's like, if you're giving it, take it.
Well, I mean, he doesn't ever I don't think I don't anticipate ever talking to him in the future. That's not in my
life plan
But I just
But I don't like how he's being treated. That's what it is
right
You know, even by people that he you know, I guess would be his
Circle his friends. I just see what
It is
And I know we and and Alexander and no we do see we do see I'm gonna look okay
I'm not gonna sit down. I'm just gonna say I'm probably gonna go to sleep now
But I want to thank you all is Andra. You're awesome
IP to wiki info
You don't have to promote it. Good. Good. Are you gonna go to bed? I'm gonna go to sleep. I think I'm gonna go to bed
But I'd love you. I love you, sweetheart. Thank you so much. We'll drink some water in the morning
I will I will everybody for being here tonight. I love y'all Zandra. I love you too. Good night people
Thank you everybody for coming here tonight
Thank you
Thank you. I'm gonna go to bed
Have a good sleep. Thank you. We're going to bed. I'll play one more on the way out.
I'll play one more on the way out. Thank you for being here.
Too much else to do, Hila. But here's the Lone Wolf song. This is Lone Wolf.
Because no matter what, I know I'm willing to and she's willing to be on her own on some of these
Thank you
They see the silence think it's empty space
Think a quiet life means a fragile place
No crowd around, no noise, no show
So they assume there's nowhere else to go
They lean back, start cutting corners slow
Late replies, let the effort go
Treat a presence like it's guaranteed
Never noticing what they're about to lose indeed
No fights, no scenes, no warnings
Just a shift you missed between the lines
You thought it bent, you thought it stayed
But it was measuring the price you paid
just to feel alive don't need a crowd just to survive
Just reality